死侍2
m -30 -8 l -29 -9 l -26 -11 l -24 -12 l -26 -14 l -28 -15 l -28 -16 l -25 -17 l -22 -17 l -22 -18 l -21 -18 l -20 -20 l -18 -20 l -16 -18 l -6 -18 l -5 -17 l -5 -12 l -6 -11 l -7 -11 l -7 -16 l -18 -16 l -19 -18 l -19 -17 l -21 -17 l -21 -15 l -22 -15 l -23 -15 l -25 -15 l -23 -13 l -23 -12 l -25 -10 l -27 -9 l -27 -8 l -23 -7 l -21 -4 l -21 -3 l -23 0 l -26 4 l -27 9 l -26 12 l -24 13 l -14 13 l -14 11 l -14 7 l -13 5 l -12 3 l -9 -1 l -7 -2 l -14 -2 l -14 1 l -15 4 l -17 5 l -19 4 l -18 3 l -17 3 l -16 1 l -16 -2 l -16 -3 l -8 -3 l -6 -3 l -5 -3 l -3 -4 l -1 -4 l -3 -5 l -4 -8 l -4 -17 l -4 -18 l -2 -18 l -2 -8 l -1 -6 l 1 -5 l 4 -5 l 6 -7 l 6 -16 l 5 -18 l 8 -18 l 9 -17 l 8 -16 l 8 -8 l 6 -5 l 4 -4 l 5 -4 l 7 -2 l 12 -4 l 12 -16 l 11 -18 l 14 -18 l 22 -7 l 22 -16 l 21 -17 l 21 -19 l 21 -20 l 22 -21 l 23 -20 l 24 -18 l 24 -16 l 25 -16 l 26 -15 l 26 -9 l 26 -8 l 25 -7 l 24 -7 l 24 -4 l 22 -4 l 14 -15 l 14 -10 l 14 -4 l 13 -4 l 7 0 l 6 2 l 4 4 l 1 4 l 3 3 l 5 2 l 6 -2 l 4 -3 l 1 -3 l 0 -1 l 0 0 l 1 1 l 3 2 l 1 2 l -1 1 l -1 -1 l -3 -3 l -4 -2 l -5 -1 l -5 2 l -4 3 l -1 3 l 2 3 l 0 4 l -3 4 l -5 4 l -6 2 l -6 -1 l -8 0 l -10 3 l -12 7 l -12 11 l -11 13 l -12 14 l -26 14 l -28 13 l -29 11 l -29 8 l -28 5 l -27 2 l -25 0 l -24 -2 l -23 -4 l -24 -6 l -28 -7 l -30 -8 m -17 -15 l -16 -15 l -13 -11 l -10 -15 l -8 -15 l -12 -10 l -8 -4 l -10 -4 l -12 -8 l -13 -8 l -14 -6 l -15 -4 l -16 -4 l -17 -4 l -14 -9 l -14 -10 l -17 -14 l -18 -15
擦枪字幕组
XGunSubTeam
原创
译制
m 0 0 b 0 5 0 9 0 14 b -1 15 -1 16 -2 17 b -4 17 -7 17 -9 17 b -9 14 -9 11 -9 8 b -9 5 -9 3 -9 0 b -9 -2 -9 -5 -9 -7 b -7 -7 -5 -7 -3 -7 b -3 -7 -3 -6 -3 -6 b -3 -6 -3 -5 -3 -5 b -4 -5 -6 -5 -7 -5 b -7 -3 -7 -1 -7 1 b -7 6 -7 10 -7 15 b -6 15 -4 15 -3 15 b -3 11 -3 7 -3 3 b -3 -1 -3 -5 -3 -9 b -3 -9 -3 -9 -3 -9 b -5 -9 -7 -9 -9 -9 b -9 -10 -9 -10 -9 -11 b -7 -11 -5 -11 -3 -11 b -3 -13 -3 -16 -3 -18 b -2 -18 0 -17 1 -17 b 1 -17 0 -16 0 -16 b 0 -14 0 -13 0 -11 b 1 -11 2 -11 3 -11 b 3 -11 3 -10 3 -10 b 2 -10 1 -10 0 -10 b 0 -9 0 -8 0 -7 b 3 -7 5 -7 8 -7 b 8 -10 8 -13 8 -16 b 8 -16 7 -16 7 -16 b 7 -17 8 -17 8 -18 b 9 -18 10 -17 11 -17 b 11 -15 11 -13 11 -11 b 18 -11 26 -11 33 -11 b 33 -11 32 -10 32 -10 b 25 -10 18 -10 11 -10 b 11 -9 11 -8 11 -7 b 18 -7 26 -7 33 -7 b 33 -7 33 -6 33 -6 b 26 -6 18 -6 11 -6 b 11 -5 11 -5 11 -4 b 11 -4 11 -3 11 -3 b 17 -3 24 -3 30 -3 b 31 -3 31 -2 32 -2 b 32 -2 33 -1 33 -1 b 33 -1 34 0 34 0 b 34 1 33 1 33 2 b 32 3 32 3 31 4 b 27 4 22 4 18 4 b 23 8 29 11 34 15 b 34 16 34 16 34 17 b 33 17 33 17 32 17 b 27 14 22 10 17 7 b 16 6 16 6 15 5 b 15 4 15 4 15 3 b 16 3 16 2 17 2 b 21 2 26 2 30 2 b 30 1 31 1 31 0 b 31 0 30 -1 30 -1 b 30 -1 29 -2 29 -2 b 23 -2 17 -2 11 -2 b 11 4 11 11 11 17 b 10 17 9 17 8 17 b 8 9 8 2 8 -6 b 5 -6 3 -6 0 -6 b 0 -4 0 -2 0 0 b -3 6 -7 11 -10 17 b -11 17 -12 17 -13 17 b -13 9 -13 2 -13 -6 b -13 -6 -14 -7 -14 -7 b -14 -7 -14 -6 -14 -6 b -14 1 -14 8 -14 15 b -15 15 -16 15 -17 15 b -17 8 -17 1 -17 -6 b -17 -6 -18 -6 -18 -6 b -18 1 -18 8 -18 15 b -19 15 -20 15 -21 15 b -21 8 -21 1 -21 -6 b -21 -6 -22 -6 -22 -6 b -22 2 -22 9 -22 17 b -23 17 -24 17 -25 17 b -25 9 -25 0 -25 -8 b -23 -8 -22 -8 -20 -8 b -20 -10 -19 -12 -19 -14 b -21 -14 -23 -14 -25 -14 b -25 -15 -25 -15 -25 -16 b -20 -16 -14 -16 -9 -16 b -9 -16 -9 -15 -9 -15 b -9 -15 -9 -14 -9 -14 b -11 -14 -13 -14 -15 -14 b -16 -12 -16 -10 -17 -8 b -15 -8 -12 -8 -10 -8 b -10 -3 -10 2 -10 7 b -10 10 -10 14 -10 17
mcar.cc
荣誉
出品
合作洽谈     Q:864413459
罗根
操你妈金刚狼
Fuck Wolverine.
先是  他抄袭我拍R级片
First, he rides my coattails with the R rating.
然后那个胡子拉碴的傻逼还靠死掉加了注
Then the hairy motherfucker ups the ante by dying.
真是傻屌
What a dick.
你猜怎么着  老狼
Well, guess what, Wolvie?
这部我也死
I'm dying in this one, too.
香 港
要想了解我为啥在四千多升
To understand why I took a cat-nap
高性能易挥发汽油上小憩
on 1,200 gallons of high-test fuel...
我得带你回到
I need to take you back
六周前的那个湿漉漉的房顶上
to the dewy slopes of six weeks ago.
我业务扩展到了海外
I'd gone international,
到处追杀杀人犯  黑帮匪徒
taking out mass murderers, gangsters,
不可言喻的恶人
unspeakable monsters.
韦德
这些人别人都不敢碰  除了我
People nobody would touch. Except me.
我要把他们摸个遍
I'm gonna touch them all over.
嗨  我是盖尔
Hey, it's Gail calling.
真喜欢你这套亮闪闪的衣服
Love the shiny suit.
很能衬托出
Really brings out
你眼中的性奴贩子
the sex trafficker in your eyes.
我不会说广东话  这位
I don't speak Cantonese, Mister...
我也别试着去读了
Well, I'm not even gonna attempt that.
但我确实上过西语八级  所以
But I did take 8th grade Spanish, so...
这句话翻译过来就是
Which literally translates to...
我不讲价  操南瓜的
I don't bargain, pumpkin fucker.
一  两  三  四
Uno, dos, tres, cuatro...
我要一杯蔓越莓柚子伏特加
I'll take a cranberry-grapefruit vodka.
我知道名字叫海风
I know it's called a Sea Breeze.
别逼我说出来
Don't make me say it.
摄影师  走起
Hit it, Dolly.
夺走罪犯枪中的手
Taking the hands out of the guns of the criminals!
西西里
喔  别到那里面去
Whoo! Do not go in there!
东京
哦天哦天  暂停暂停
Oh, God! Oh, God, time out! Time out!
卡  坏人的血进我眼罩里去了
Cut. Got bad guy blood, right in my open eye.
呃  真恶心
Oh, that's so gross.
操
Fuck.
童军服务员凯文
Scoutmaster Kevin?
比洛克西
太性感了
Too exotic?
我的世界巡游把我带回家
My world tour brought me home
见到了这位  谢尔盖瓦·利什尼科夫
to this guy, Sergei Valishnikov.
家  甜蜜的家
我们回头再说他
But we'll get to him in a moment.
因为我知道你们在想什么
'Cause I know what you're thinking.
还好我把孩子留家了
"I'm so glad I left the kiddos at home."
但这你就错了
But that's where you'd be wrong.
你的那位保姆现在可是嗨翻了天
That babysitter of yours is high as fuck right now...
翻译：萨诸塞de召唤X2
而且  信不信吧  死侍2是个合家欢的电影
and, believe it or not, Deadpool 2 is a family film.
翻译：萌梦同学
真的
True story.
而且每部优秀的合家欢电影都从一场恶劣的谋杀开始
And every good family film starts with a vicious murder.
翻译：Agnes Lee
小鹿斑比  狮子王  电锯惊魂7
Bambi, The Lion King, Saw 7.
翻译：柠檬
霍日尼玛  这家伙着火了
Holy shit pickles! That guy's on fire.
翻译：银子小狐狸
这可不是电脑特效  朋友们  他真的着火了
That's not CGI, folks. He's actually on fire.
是啊  你们知道我杀坏人能拿钱的吧
Yeah. You know I get paid to take out bad guys, right?
翻译：胡小华
但这个家伙
But this guy?
翻译：苏打
他是最坏的那种
He was one of the worst of 'em.
翻译：也罢
快点把这扇破门给我打开
Hurry up and open this fucking door,
然后咱们一起杀了这个傻逼
and let's kill this motherfucker!
校对：萨诸塞de召唤
特效：小螺号
呃  真恶心
Ugh. So gross.
总监：麦斯
还有安全屋  认真的吗
A panic room? Really?
你能出来吗
Can you come out?
我真的该走了  今天我过纪念日
I really have to go. It's my anniversary.
一遍又一遍  我总听人说
Over and over, I hear people say,
我就是没有那么多自信
"I just don't have enough confidence."
听着  自信不是你随便就有的东西
Listen, confidence is not something you have.
是你要制造的东西
It's something you create.
而且你可以在任何时候制造自信
And you can create it at any moment in time.
自信感不过就是
A sense of confidence is nothing
对自己内心的力量的感知
but a sense of power within yourself...
确信自己能做成某件事
a sense of certainty that you can pull something off.
快开车  快他妈开车
Start the car! Start the fucking car!
都朋德
Dopinder!
快他妈开车
Start the fucking car!
- 喔  - 噢  我拉裤子了
- Whoo! - Oh, I shit my pants.
其实可能是我
Actually, that may have been me.
任务完成了
Oh, mission accomplished?
嗯  像小布什完成伊战那种吧
Well, in a George W. Sort of way.
2003年小布什曾经做过一个《任务完成》
的演讲声称在伊拉克的主要战斗已经结束
这傻逼不可能永远呆在安全屋里
Fucker can't stay in a panic room forever.
你真是活出了梦想  死哥
Oh, you're living the dreams, DP.
这一路上够受了  都朋德
It has been quite the run, Dopinder,
而且谁能想到呢
and who'da thought?
现在我开始和耶稣说一样的话了
Now I'm talked about in the same sentence as Jesus.
《耶稣受难记》  然后是我
Passion of the Christ, then me.
至少是在国内
At least domestically.
海外市场我们赚得多
We beat them overseas,
那边没有宗教这种事
where there's no such thing as religion.
我也想活出梦想  阿侍
I do want to live the dreams, Pool Boy.
开出租没有看上去那么性感
Taxiing is not as sexy as it looks.
- 我想填满我的  - 兜么
- I want to fill my... - Pockets?
你喜欢啥  来点  嗯  可卡因
What's your poison? A little, uh, cokey cokey?
不上网买鞋
Can't maintain an erection
就硬不起来
without buying shoes online?
最后这个我没经历过
I've never experienced that last one.
说说看  小子
Talk to me, Goose.
我是说灵魂  我想填满我的灵魂
I was going to say "soul". I want to fill my soul.
我想要属于某件事  像你一样  侍先生
I want to belong to something, like you, Pool, sir.
- 都朋德  - 嗯
- Dopinder... - Hmm?
你总是能让我惊讶
You never cease to surprise me.
你知道吗  你内心的深度实在非凡
You know, the depth of your heart is extraordinary.
我们都需要一点归属感
We all need a sense of belonging.
我们都需要真正的家的感觉
We all need a genuine sense of home.
世界中的一个位置
A place in this world.
我想成为一个职业杀手
I want to become a contract killer.
抱歉  你说啥
I'm sorry. What did you say?
还记得我之前绑架了班度
Remember when I kidnapped Bandhu
还威胁他要施以巨大的暴力
and threatened him with great violence?
你其实杀死了他
You kind of killed him.
然后记得那部电影么  《夜访吸血鬼》
And then remember the movie Interview with the Vampire?
不想记得
Don't want to.
里面汤姆·克鲁斯第一次
When Tom Cruise fed
喂十岁的克斯汀·邓斯特
10-year-old Kirsten Dunst blood
喝血
for the first time...
然后她抬头看向他圆滑
and she looked up at his smooth,
帅气的脸  然后说
handsome face and said...
我还要
"I want some more."
哦阿侍  把我想成十岁的克斯汀·邓斯特
Oh, Pool, picture me, a 10-year-old Kirsten Dunst.
我永远都没法不想这个画面
I'll never not picture that.
但我真的等不及永远不这样说
But I can't wait to never speak of this,
越早越好
as soon as possible.
我们到了
We're here.
你是我的汤姆·克鲁斯
You're my Tom Cruise!
而你是我的克里斯汀·邓斯特
And you're my Kristen Dunst!
克里斯汀  还是克斯汀
Kristen? Kirsten?
抱歉  我来晚了
Sorry I'm late.
有一帮
There was a bunch of
不残不疾的小孩困在了一棵树上
handicapable children stuck in a tree...
- 然后我不得不  - 不对
- and I had to, uh... - Uh-uh.
你是对的  我在和一个穿斗篷的狠角色打架
You're right. I was fighting a caped badass.
详见《正义黎明》
然后我们发现他妈妈名字也叫玛莎
But then we discovered his mom is named Martha, too.
不对
No.
堵车了
Traffic?
快来狠狠亲我  小红
Kiss me like you miss me, Red.
你来啊
Well, come here.
我去洗个澡然后脱掉这身衣服
I'm gonna shower and get out of this suit.
你不想要你的惊喜吗
Don't you want your surprise?
我像是个有耐心的烧伤患么
Do I look like a patient burn victim?
我也给你买了礼物
I got one for you, too.
纪念日快乐  宝贝
Happy anniversary, baby.
打开打开打开
Open, open, open.
木滚球游戏币
Skee-Ball token.
咱们第一次约会
Our first date.
是滴
Yup.
那是真的  高级别铅
That's genuine, high-grade lead.
我永远都会留着
I'll keep it forever.
谢谢  宝贝
Thank you, baby.
- 看你的礼物  - 好吧
- Open yours. - All right, all right.
哦
Oh...
这真是我见过的最漂亮的
That's just the most beautiful thing that I've...
我不知道这是啥
I don't know what this is.
我的IUD
My IUD.
炸弹吗[IED]
A bomb?
不是  什么屌脑子  我的避孕环
No, dick for brains. My birth control device.
啥  你是说你的
What, you mean that your...
宝宝工厂开工啦
Baby factory's open for business.
哦我的天
Oh, my God!
哦我天  我想要个儿子
Oh, my God! I want a boy!
或者一个小姑娘  绝对是二者之一
Or a little girl! Definitely one or the other!
然后我想让我们孩子只有名没有姓
Oh! And I want our kid to have only one name.
像雪儿  或者陶德
Like Cher or Todd.
你得先让我怀上  牛仔
You gotta pump a baby in me first, cowboy.
是的
Yes, I do.
咱们去看点黄片  然后让那张床知道谁是大佬
Let's watch some porn and show that bed who's boss.
来吧
Let's do that.
爸爸
* Papa...
你能听到我吗
* Can you hear me?
爸爸  你能看到我吗
* Papa, can you see me?
这首歌你耳熟吗
Does this song sound familiar to you?
梅
May.
康纳  如果是男孩  梅  如果是男孩
Connor, if it's a boy. May, if it's a girl.
真奇怪
So weird.
家庭对我来说一直都是屁
Family was always an F-word to me.
我那个屎一样的爹消失了
My pile of shit father took off and bailed.
我是说  我也没有多少强势的榜样
I mean, it's not like I have a lot of strong role models
能讲给陶德听
to draw off of for Todd.
喂  听我说
Hey. Look at me.
你不是你爹
You are not your father.
更何况
Besides...
我永远  永远  不会让我们的孩子叫陶德的
I will never, ever let our child be named Todd.
但问题在这里
But here's the thing,
这些事情不都是这样的么
isn't that how it always works?
好比《星球大战》
Like in Star Wars,
男人注定成为他们的父亲
men are destined to become their father...
然后和他们的妹妹发生双方同意的性行为
and then have consensual sex with their sister?
我觉得你那部电影完全完全理解错了
I think you missed big, big chunks of that movie.
不是  我很确定卢克上了她
No, I'm pretty sure Luke nailed her.
宝贝  那是《帝国反击战》
Baby, that's Empire.
关键在于  孩子
The point is, kids...
他们给我们一个超越自己的机会
they give us a chance to be better than we are.
比我们之前好多了
Better than we used to be.
你比我长得聪明多了
You're a lot smarter than I look.
我打算做个甜点
I'm gonna go make dessert.
你带上假鸡鸡  我们来造个超级小宝贝
You get the strap-on. Let's make a super baby.
我知道这事不是这么做的  但是我们可以试试
Pretty sure it doesn't work that way, but we can try.
克里斯塔怎么样  但是是K打头
What about Krystal? But with a "K"?
太像脱衣舞娘了
It's too stripper-y.
凯文K打头
Kevin with a "K"!
不  也太像脱衣舞郎了
No, too stripper-y, too.
厄尔
Uh, Earl!
要是管他叫厄尔  肯定直接
He's gonna go straight to jail
就进监狱了吧
if we name him Earl.
布鲁斯咋样
What about Bruce?
不
No.
趴下
Get down.
怎么了
What?
宝贝  宝贝
Baby? Baby?
我没事
I'm okay.
谢天谢地我还没用上奶油刀
Thank God I didn't have to use the cream cheese spreader.
不要
Please.
不要  不要
Please. Please.
亲爱的  对不起
Baby, I'm so sorry.
不
No!
出品人
等等
制片人：你是杀了她吗
联合制片方：我不明白
演员：明显，某个不像和别人分享聚光灯的人
微笑  等闪光灯
编剧：真正的反派
摄影师：瞎子艾尔
导演：《疾速追杀》里面杀死那条狗的人
爸爸  你能听到我吗
* Papa, can you hear me?
是我吗  还是
Is it just me, or does
《冰雪奇缘》里的  你想不想堆雪人
Do You Want to Build a Snowman? from Frozen...
听起来就像是
sound suspiciously like
《燕特尔》里的的插曲  爸爸  你能听到我吗
Papa, Can You Hear Me? From Yentl?
爸爸  你能听到我吗
* Papa, can you hear me?
然而谁他妈都没意识到
And nobody fucking realizes it.
回家吧  你都在这儿待了三天了
Go home. You've been here for three days, okay?
你现在闻上去就像是一个内战的伤腐烂之后
You smell like somebody shit in a Civil War wound...
还有人往里面拉了泡屎
after it had become gangrenous.
他们就应该直接截肢  还拉泡屎干啥
They should've just amputated it. Why shit in it?
毫无道理
Doesn't make any sense.
我喜欢《冰雪奇缘》
I love Frozen.
我爱她  我爱她就像是大海爱着水
I loved her. I loved her like an ocean loves water.
大海就是水啊
An ocean is water.
更重要的是  我喜欢她  我真的真的喜欢她  你懂吗
More importantly, I liked her. I really liked her, you know?
乔治·迈克尔说得对
George Michael was right.
我再也无法跳舞了  妈的
I'm never gonna dance again. Fuck!
他也是个死人了
He's dead, too.
至少我们还有大卫·鲍伊呀
At least we still have Bowie.
是啊  我们  还有鲍伊
Yeah. We still have Bowie.
对不起
I'm sorry.
一杯一杯复一杯
Shot after shot,
也改变不了事实啊  我觉得你
it's not gonna change the fact that I think you're...
你是在尿尿吗  你在小便吗
Are you pissing? Are you urinating right now?
你现在一副小便时的表情
You're making the face that you make when you urinate.
- 他是在尿尿吗  - 我来了
- Is he pissing? - I'm on it!
你收拾好  都朋德
There you go, Dopinder.
如果你想成为一名职业杀手
If you want to be a contract killer...
你得在学会握枪之前学会握拖把
you gotta handle a mop before you handle a gun.
但是我没感觉这两者之间
Although I don't quite understand
有什么共同之处
how they are at all similar.
它们都有把儿  现在你给我走开
Well, they both have handles. Now, leave me.
韦德  回家吧
Go home, Wade.
我已经没有家了  黄鼠狼  你知道吧  我
I don't have a home, Weas, you know. I got a...
妈的  好了  我没事
Fuck! Okay, I'm fine.
我没事
I'm fine.
韦德  你知道没事是什么意思吗
You know what "fine" stands for, Wade?
玩鸡巴蛋  没安全感  缺爱  情绪化
Fucked up, insecure, needy, and emotional.
根据
According to the...
- 库柏勒·罗斯  - 对
- Kubler-Ross. - Yeah.
根据库柏勒·罗斯的模型
According to the Kubler-Ross model...
否认只是哀伤的五个阶段之一
denial is just one of the five stages of grief.
天啊  巴克
Jesus Christ, Buck!
你没台词了
No more speaking lines for you.
韦德的可卡因
复明药方
我正在考虑
"I'm thinking it over!"
妈个巴子的
Motherfuck!
妈蛋
Fuck!
你他妈的来这儿干什么
The hell you doin' here?
你不懂什么叫敲门吗
Don't you know how to knock?
我还以为你看到我了
I thought you saw me...
用你的耳朵
with your ears.
你很幸运我没有一枪打烂你的
You're lucky I didn't shoot you in the...
墙吗
The wall?
还是冰箱  我太痛苦了
The refrigerator? I'm in so much pain.
亲爱的  我听说了
I heard the news, sweetie.
我很抱歉  真的
I'm very sorry. I am.
我该怎么办  艾尔
What am I gonna do, Al?
也许得做些可怕的事
Probably something terrible.
我懂你
Knowing you.
都是我的错
It was my fault.
是我搞成这样的
I fucking did this.
我只想扶着她  看着她
And all I wanna do is grab her and see her
跟她说声对不起  但我不能
and tell her that I'm sorry, and I can't.
她不在了
She's gone.
甜心  你说话能大声一点吗
Sweetheart, can you speak up?
你嘴里就像噙了个鸡巴似的
It's a little hard to hear you
根本听不清你在说什么
with that pity dick in your mouth.
你听好了  甜心  你得继续活下去
Now, look, sugar. You need to just keep living.
谢谢你
Thank you...
马修·麦康纳  你可真是字字珠玑
Matthew McConaughey, your words are a treasure.
倾听痛苦
Listen to the pain.
痛苦既是历史老师还是算命先生
It's both history teacher and fortune teller.
韦德  痛苦教会我们做人
Pain teaches us who we are, Wade.
有时候  事情很糟糕  觉得自己就快要死了
Sometimes, it's so bad, we feel like we're dying.
但是我们要是没死过又怎么能真正生活呢  是吧
But we can't really live till we've died a little, can we?
韦德
Wade?
- 韦德  - 我在这儿呢  艾尔西娅
- Wade? - I'm right here, Althea.
这简直就是我听过的
And that is the most beautiful thing
最优美的句子
I've ever heard.
你说得很对
You're absolutely right.
我是要去做些可怕的事
I'm about to do something terrible.
知道了  都说完了
There. All caught up.
但是我们要是没死过又怎么能真正生活呢
You can't really live until you've died a little.
咱们来试试这理论吧
Let's test that theory, shall we?
婴儿工厂开业了
Baby factory's open for business.
咱俩一样疯狂
Your crazy matches my crazy.
我永远  永远  不会让我们的孩子叫陶德的
I will never, ever let our child be named Todd.
木滚球游戏币
Skee-Ball token.
国际妇女节快乐
Happy International Women's Day.
我一直在想
Listen, I've been thinking a lot.
是吗
Really?
为什么我们在一起这么幸福
About why we're so good together.
我爱你  韦德·威尔逊
I love you, Wade Wilson.
妮莎
Ness?
Ness.
妮莎  这里有些什么  我靠近不了你
Ness, there's something here. I can't get to you.
你的心  没有在正确的地方
Your heart's not in the right place.
等等  什么啊
Wait, hold on. What?
你的心  没有在正确的地方
Your heart's not in the right place.
等等  什么意思
Wait. What do you mean
你说我的心没有在正确的地方  是什么意
my heart's not in the right place? What does it...
节哀吧  韦德  我也很难过
I'm terribly sorry for your loss, Wade.
你都碎了
You're broken.
哦  天啊  我知道这是谁
Oh, God. I know that voice.
心在正确的地方
"Heart's in the right place."
心在正确的  这是什么意思
"Heart's in the right..." What does that mean?
你已经睡了三天了
You've been sleep for three days.
我顺便给你穿上了衣服
I took the liberty of dressing you.
不他妈是吧
No shit.
为什么我他妈死不了
Why can't I fucking die?
韦德  把面具摘了
Take your mask off, Wade.
我们得谈谈
We must talk.
你得重新开始
You need fresh start.
经过训练  你也能当X战警
With training, you can be X-Man.
你这就是在浪费时间  发光的耶稣
You're wasting your time, Shiny Jesus.
我当不了X战警
I'm not X-Man material.
年度最保守陈述
Understatement of the year.
韦德  这是雪绪
Wade, Yukio.
雪绪  这是韦德
Yukio, Wade.
这特娘的是什么个情况
What in the fuck knuckles is this?
她是我女票  你这个心胸狭窄的混蛋
She's my girlfriend, you intolerant shit.
哇哦  别喷  福克斯和朋友
Whoa! Pump the hate brakes, Fox & Friends.
我只是想不到竟然还有人跟你约会
I'm just surprised anyone would date you.
尤其还是小马宝莉里的萍琪派
Especially Pinkie Pie from My Little Pony.
我喜欢这个家伙
I like this guy.
等着瞧吧
Give him a chance.
看到你这样挺好的
It's great seeing you like this.
是呢
Yeah.
拜拜  韦德
Bye, Wade!
现在  你在我们家屋檐下就得有点规矩
Now, some ground rules while under our roof.
第一条  不能杀人
"Rule number one. No killing...
谁都不行  再坏也不能杀
"anyone ever, no matter how bad.
第二条  冰箱里的东西都得贴标签
"Rule two. Label everything in refrigerator."
韦德
Wade?
Wade!
别想着追过来
Don't try to chase me.
我可不想让你再碰我了
I'm not ready to be touched again.
墙上挂的这么多白人老哥哥
All these elderly white men on the walls...
真该把我的强奸报警哨带来
Should have brought my rape whistle.
你好
Hi.
那东西在它倒下去之后就坏了
Those were already damaged after they fell there!
说到底  我在这儿到底该干点儿啥
What am I supposed to do around here, anyway?
和一群人坐成一圈  大谈我的心里感受吗
Sit in a share circle, talk about my feelings?
这我又能怎么做
And how would I do that exactly?
这里的人到底跑哪儿去了
'Cause where the fuck is everyone?
总是只有你
It's always just you
和负音波少年有史以来最长名字
and Negasonic Teenage Longest Name Ever...
够了
Enough!
我说了别摸我
I said no touching!
干鸡毛啊
What the fuck?
还以为公司能给我点好处呢
You'd think the studio would throw us a bone.
他们就不能扔来一个著名X战警吗
They can't just dust off one of the famous X-Men?
好比说那个长着大鸽子翅膀的家伙
How 'bout that putz with the giant pigeon wings?
说回来这翅膀有啥用啊
What do those do anyway, huh?
学校
把他带离地面三尺
Carry him three feet off the ground
就为抢夺最近的松饼屑吗
to snatch up the nearest muffin crumb?
不  不  不
No, no, no!
我完全不是X战警那块料
I am not X-Man material at all.
首先
First off...
我都不是处了  其次  再者
I'm not even a virgin. Second and more...
我本可以留你一个人
I should have left you
继续自怨自艾去
in the self-pitying mess I found you in.
但是朋友就是这样  有需要就出现
But this is what friends do. They show up!
并不是在方便或者容易的时候
Not when convenient or easy.
而是在艰难时刻  而你总是把事情变得很艰难
When hard, and you always make it hard.
你不健康
You are unwell.
带你过来都费了我老鼻子劲
I'm sticking my neck out bringing you here.
等等  有一个害死
Wait. One of the assholes
凡妮莎的人活下来了
who killed Vanessa got away.
哦  我的老天啊
Oh, Jesus Christ!
韦德  不管是谁
Wade, whoever they are...
我们都去找到他们  将他们绳之以法
we track them down and bring them to justice.
是我
It was me.
我就是幸存的那个混蛋
I'm the asshole who got away.
我把他们每一个都杀了  除了我
I killed every last one of them, except me.
我杀不死自己
Couldn't kill me.
我们本来准备要孩子了
We were gonna start a family.
我们原本
We were, uh...
原本会成为一家人
We were gonna be a family.
韦德
Wade...
凡妮莎死了  不会回来了
Vanessa is gone. She's not coming back.
这也许不是你想要的家
This may not be family you want...
但是这是你需要的家
but it's family you need.
你有一颗善良的心
You have a good heart.
它属于这里  可以成长
It belongs here where it can grow.
你怎么说
What did you say?
我的心
About my heart?
也许我是在正确的地方
I think I'm in the right place.
韦德
Wade.
Wade!
我只是试试脑波增强仪
Hey, I was just taking Cerebro for a spin here...
凝视着未来
looking deep into the future.
哎妈  这玩意儿
Phew. This thing...
- 脑波仪不是这么用的  - 脑波仪不是这么用的
- That's not how Cerebro works. - That's not how Cerebro works.
是的  是的  没错
Yes. Yes, it is.
- 我们有任务了  - 我们有任务了
- We have mission. - We have mission.
我们有  你有
We do. You do.
出门要注意安全哦
You guys be safe out there.
- 不  我想让你也加入  - 不  我想让你也加入
- No, I want you to join. - No, you want me to join.
抱歉  你说啥
I'm sorry, what?
你准备好了
You are ready.
这主意糟透了  绝对没好下场
That's a terrible idea, and it's gonna end badly.
你想知道我怎么知道的么  给你个提示
You wanna know how I know? I'll give you a hint.
就在我的头上
It's on my head
闻上去一股帕特里克·斯图尔特的味儿
and smells like Patrick Stewart.
五分钟上X战机
Be at the X-Jet in five.
艾琳·梅里韦瑟  来自WHIT新闻台
Irene Merryweather, WHIT News.
为您现场直播在埃塞克斯变种人收容中心
Live here at a breaking news situation
发生的紧急状况
at the Essex House for Mutant Rehabilitation.
一位变种男孩似乎
A mutant boy is appearing to have
出了某种事故
some sort of an incident...
- 警察就在我身后  - 离我远点
- with police here behind me. - Get away from me!
已经有两辆警车被掀翻
There are two police vehicles that are overturned.
- 现场有交火  - 滚开  滚远点
- There are open fires. - Fuck off! Stay back!
现场一片混乱
A scene of absolute chaos here.
冷静下
Calm down.
我烧死你信不  你往后退
I'll burn you! You stay back!
离我远点
Get away from me!
你他妈是想死么
You wanna fucking die?
看来X战警已经抵达现场
And it appears as if the X-Men are arriving...
靠边靠边
Scatter!
还貌似带了个学员
With what appears to be a trainee.
大家  冷静  专业人士到了
Everyone, calm down! The pros are here. I...
我们是X战警
We're the X-Men!
六十年代用来影射种族歧视的一个过时的隐喻
A dated metaphor for racism in the '60s.
在这一比喻中，变种人影射黑人，X教授影射
马丁路德金，而万磁王则影射激进派领袖马尔科姆X
所以  尊敬
So, respect.
稍息  警官
At ease, Officer.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
这是我的工作
My job!
你说我准备好了的
You're the one who said I was ready,
我是相当的不同意
and I frankly disagreed with you.
但是既然来都来了  那就求同存异吧
But here we are, trying to overcome our differences.
就像碧昂斯唱的
Like Beyonce says, "Please...
请别  请别再欺骗我了
"Please, stop cheating on me."
嘿
Hey!
这是第五次事故了
This is the fifth incident.
这个小子应该被关在冰盒里  而不是这里
This kid needs to be in the Ice Box, not here.
罗素应该由我们照顾
Russell belongs in our care.
而不是监狱  我保证
Not in prison. I assure you...
一切都在控制之中
we have everything under control.
滚远点  否则烧你
Stay back! I'll burn you!
我咋没觉得哪里有
Not getting a real
“控制之中”了  马蒂
"under control" vibe here, Marty.
- 是叫格伦吧  - 丹尼尔
- It is Glen, isn't it? - Daniel.
我来负责问问题  让我跟这个孩子聊聊
I'll ask the questions. Let me talk to the kid.
你就在这里  翘着你那奇怪  性感的嘴唇吧
You stay here with your weird, secret sex lips.
你想死啊
You wanna die?
这个小子真可爱
This kid's adorable.
我不知道为啥我还带了空尖弹
I don't know why I packed the hollow points.
把你蛋蛋烧掉你信不信
I'll burn your balls off!
第一天  有点小紧张
First day. I'm so nervous!
你刚是不是说空尖弹了
Did you just say "hollow points"?
对  早知道带
Yeah, probably should've
呲水枪了
brought a Super Soaker.
嗨  你好啊
Hi, there!
退后  否则这个贾斯汀·比伯就去死吧
Stay back or Justin Bieber dies!
贾斯汀·比伯  他叫你贾斯汀·比伯
Justin Bieber. He called you Justin Bieber.
别急  等等
Hold on! Wait, wait, wait!
好了  你要做什么先停停
Okay, let's not do whatever that is.
好么  咱们先聊聊
Okay? Let's just talk!
你叫罗素  是么
It's Russell, right?
- 火拳  - 火拳啊
- Firefist. - Firefist.
哎呦  名字不错哦  都是哪里烧起来啊
Ooh, that's a great name. Where does it burn?
只有拳头  还是连着胳膊肘一起
Just the fist, or all the way up to the elbow?
绝对连着胳膊肘一起了
Definitely all the way up to the elbow.
放弃抵抗  否则就有麻烦了
Come quietly, or there will be trouble.
- 你抄袭机械战警的台词  - 是机械战警里的
- You stole that from Robocop! - That's from Robocop!
你往后站吧
Just stand down!
要尴尬死我了  听着  火
You're embarrassing me. Look, Fire...
我的天  我说不出来  真抱歉
Oh, my God! I can't say it! I'm so sorry!
哦  操  我受够了
Oh, shit! That fucking does it!
双手放在膝盖后
Put your hands behind your knees
头着地跪下  快
and get down on your head! Now!
韦德  第一条规矩是什么
Wade! What was first rule?
冰箱里的东西要贴标签
Label everything in the refrigerator!
- 不要让情况更危急  - 规矩就是用来打破的
- Do not escalate! - Rules are meant to be broken!
这完全与规矩的
That's the exact opposite
用途相反
of what they're meant for!
操  好吧
Fuck! Fine!
我重新开始
I'll start from the beginning.
我叫做死侍  我是X战警
My name is Deadpool, and I'm an X-Man.
- 的学员  - 憋说话
- Trainee! - Shut it!
好了  我知道了
Look, I get it.
你很害怕
All right, you're scared.
孤独一人
Alone.
没有家人
You got no family.
我也没有家人
I didn't have a family, either.
你住这破地儿  你猜怎么着
You live in this dump. Guess what?
我以前也住这种破地儿
I used to live in a shithole just like it.
但我告诉你  事情还可以更坏
But you know something? To make matters worse...
青春期比较迷茫很正常
it's a confusing time in your life right now.
身体在发生一系列火热的变化
Your body is going through some fiery changes.
有点过了  是不有点过了
Too far? I went too far, didn't I?
这下刺激了
That was effervescent.
好好上学哦  小盆友
Stay in school, kid.
不上也没事  我就没
Or don't. I didn't.
现在不还当上X战警了
And I'm an X-Man.
学员
Trainee.
妈逼的
Fuck it!
超级英雄式着陆就要来了
Superhero landing coming up!
英雄玉米片
瑞安?雷诺兹
哦  操  操  操
Ah, fuck, fuck, fuck!
一点都不实用嘛
That is so not practical.
X战警还是当得挺爽的
I could get used to this X-Man shit.
学员
Trainee!
快给他带上能力抑制环
Get a power restraint on him. Now!
放轻松  小伙子  没戏了  抓到你了
Calm down, squirt. It's over. We got ya.
那玩意儿是干嘛的
What's that do?
能力削弱项圈
Power-dampening collar.
抑制所有变种能力
Shuts down all mutant abilities.
除非拿个手雷才能把它取下来
You can't get it off. Unless you've got a grenade.
哈  第一幕就该用上的
Huh. Could've used one of those in the first act.
谢谢你
Thank you!
那简直太刺激了
That was absolutely thrilling.
真正的英雄
True heroism in action.
我们都欠你的
We are in your debt.
我们接手就好了
We can take it from here.
带我去冰盒  求你
Take me to the Ice Box, please!
哪里都比这里好
Anywhere's better than here.
相信我孩子
Believe me, son,
你不会想去冰盒的
you do not wanna go to the Ice Box.
进去吧  小伙子
Let's get you inside, young man.
不  等等
No, wait, wait. Wait.
你们呆在这儿
You guys stay there.
那些人有伤害你
Those guys hurt you?
谁
Who?
那个秃子  还是那个贾里德·库什纳
Baldilocks? Jared Kushner?
他们俩
Both of 'em?
哦  操他妈
Oh, fuck it.
四五个瞬间
Four or five moments!
你说啥
I'm sorry?
四五个瞬间
Four or five moments!
成为英雄只需要这么多
That's all it takes to be a hero.
人们以为你起床起得英雄
People think you wake up a hero...
刷牙刷得英雄
brush your teeth a hero...
射进洗手液瓶射得英雄
ejaculate into a soap dispenser a hero.
但不  成为英雄  只需要那么几个瞬间
But, no, being a hero takes only a few moments!
几个瞬间
A few moments...
做无人愿为之事
doing the ugly stuff no one else will do.
不
No!
退下  别开火
Stand down! Hold your fire!
- 韦德  你做了什么  - 钢力士  不要
- Wade, what did you do? - Colossus, no!
那个孩子被虐待了  你能看出来
That kid was abused! You can tell.
- 一直都能看出来  - 我们有规矩的
- You can always tell! - We have rules!
你不是法官  陪审团  或者行刑官
You are not judge, jury or executioner!
去他妈的规则  我只为正义而战
Fuck your rules! I fight for what's right!
即使有时需要耍阴招
And sometimes you gotta fight dirty!
这是你最后一次让我失望  韦德
You let me down for the last time, Wade.
好了  把这几个押上车
Okay, get these guys in the pod.
把他们带去冰盒
Take them to the Ice Box.
嘿  宝贝儿
Hey, baby!
我想知道我会加入哪个帮派哎
I wonder what gang I'll be in.
好
Yeah!
- 是要用分院帽分配吗  - 你好啊
- Is there, like, a Sorting Hat? - Hi.
变种人
走你的路
Go!
往左  傻逼
Hard left, douchebag.
来  你先请
Please, after you.
又有一个恶心的变种人被关起来了呢
Another disgusting mutant off the streets.
天佑美国
God bless America.
走  我们去吃个玉米饼吧
Let's get a taco.
晚安  你这个烦人精
Nighty-night, you annoying prick!
让我来告诉你最大的谎言是什么
I'mma tell you what the big lie is.
是厕纸
Toilet paper.
普通厕纸就像是一道美味开胃菜
Toilet paper is a plenty fine appetizer.
但是  再后来就有了
But, then...
好奇牌天然呵护湿纸巾
Huggies Natural Care wet wipes.
这是你的主菜
That's your main course.
它们很柔软  很滋润  很适合给小孩子使用
They're soft, they're moist. They're for babies.
最后  再给厕纸一个机会
Finally, one more pass with the toilet paper,
也许拿来擦干净多余的水
maybe clear out that excess moisture.
也许再吹那么一下
Maybe treat yourself to a blow and go,
如果你有吹风机的话
if you can get you a hair dryer.
只要三十秒  就能给你完美体验
Just about 30 seconds will do you good.
你踏马啥玩意儿啊
The fuck?
哪年
Year?
啥
What?
今年是哪一年
What year is it?
这什么傻逼问题
What kind of dumb-ass question is that to ask?
你离你的超能力很远了
You're a long way from your superpowers.
是啊
Yeah.
操
Fuck!
我想当个超级英雄
I wanted to be a superhero.
一直想要一套真正地超级英雄战衣
Always wanted a real super suit.
后来呢
What happened?
你见过我这种肥胖体型的超级英雄吗
When was the last time you saw a plus-sized superhero?
没见过吧
Never.
真是业界歧视
The industry discriminates.
去你妈的超级英雄
Fuck superheroes.
去你妈的世界
Fuck everyone.
我从这里出去的第一件事就是
The first thing I wanna do when I get out of here...
把那校长活活烧死
burn the headmaster alive...
然后和他烧焦的尸体自拍玩儿
and then take a selfie with his smoldering corpse.
谁说的监狱不能有感化作用来着
Who says prison isn't reformative?
那傻逼痛恨变种人
Fucker hates mutants.
愿上帝保佑
Blessed are the wicked
经我手治愈之恶人
who are healed by my hand.
人类不是变种人类
你的能力
Your abilities.
我知道它们很有吸引力
I know how seductive they are.
现在  请你别哭
Now, please don't cry.
明天  我们就去找这里块头最大的人
Tomorrow, we'll find the biggest guy in here...
然后我们把他变成我们的
and we'll make him our...
什么情况
What was that?
这动静就是块头最大那兄弟弄的
That is the biggest guy in here.
关于冰盒的有趣小知识
Fun fact about the Ice Box...
尽管没有人见过
though no one's ever seen it,
但是他们在地下室里关了个怪物
they keep a monster in the basement.
旁边就是一大碗
Right next to a huge,
冒着烟的伏笔
steaming bowl of foreshadowing.
听着
Look.
我没办法保护你
I can't protect you.
只要带着这个项圈
With this collar on,
我的超能力就只剩下了在我体内奔腾咆哮的癌细胞了
my superpower is just unbridled cancer.
要是给我一套弓箭的话  我和鹰眼差不多
Give me a bow and arrow, I'm basically Hawkeye.
现在  如果你不介意的话
Now, if you'll excuse me...
我还有好几个肿瘤要长呢  凡妮莎还在等我
I've got tumors to grow. Vanessa awaits.
我就从给咱们做个刀开始吧
I'll start by making us a shank.
- 你真听话  - 我偷了那个警卫的钢笔
- Good listening. - I stole that guard's pen...
然后藏到了传统监狱钱包里
and stashed it in the old prison wallet,
你懂的
if you know what I'm saying.
监狱钱包
Prison wallet?
我是真心希望我不懂你在说什么
I really hope I don't know what you're saying.
我能听见你在那儿翻腾
I can hear you rummaging around in there.
为您带来在此前
And to update you
报道的事故之后续
on the story reported earlier,
在埃塞克斯
after a lengthy standoff
变种人收容中心外面的长时间对峙后
outside the Essex House for Mutant Rehabilitation...
两名变种人被捕
two mutants were arrested
并被押送到了冰盒监狱
and transported to the Ice Box...
进入修复模式
Entering repair mode.
数辆警车被毁
Several police cars were destroyed
X战警被呼叫到现场控制场面
and the X-Men were called in to restore order.
医务人员现在
Cells seven and nine
禁止进入七号及九号牢房
now off-limits for medical personnel.
医务人员现在
Cells seven and nine
禁止进入七号及九号牢房
now off-limits for medical personnel.
别这样
Don't do that.
啥玩意儿  你为什么在冲我抛媚眼儿
What? Why are you winking at me?
我来照应你
I got your back.
噢  主啊
Oh, my God.
你病了  我要保护你
You're sick, I gotta protect you.
让我一个人待会儿吧  孩子
Just leave me alone, kid.
哦  真棒
Oh, great.
你们好啊  小鲜肉们
Well, hello there, new fish.
能在这儿看到点新面孔真棒
It's nice to see some fresh faces around here.
我做过点商品目录的模特
I've done some light catalog work...
但是说实话  当模特不过是成为演员之路上的垫脚石而已
but, really, modeling is just a stepping stone to acting.
- 我在跟他说话  - 哦
- I was talking to him. - Oh.
我们见过吗  你那胡子我一时想不起来是谁啊
Have we met? I can't place your mustache.
- 我是黑色汤姆·卡西迪  - 我是白色韦德·威尔逊
- Black Tom Cassidy. - White Wade Wilson.
你的超能力是什么  文化挪用吗
What's your superpower? Cultural appropriation?
你本该是这里最厉害的傻逼的
You're supposed to be the toughest cunt in here.
但我觉得你看上去不像
You don't look like much to me.
放风区的天字号第一准则  傻逼
First rule of the yard, fuckface...
找到最强壮的那个人  然后把他变成你的
find the biggest guy and make him your...
第二强壮的人
Second biggest guy.
我现在最不需要的就是被传染肝炎了
The last thing I need is more hepatitis.
噢  还滑溜溜的耶  这张桌子该擦一擦了
Oh, it's slippery, too. This table needs a wipe down!
有人能帮我擦一擦这张桌子吗
Can we get a wipe down on the table?
小子  我觉得你站错队了
Kid, I think you picked the wrong side.
不  我没有  他是我朋友
No, I didn't! He's my friend!
闭嘴  我们不是朋友
Zip it. We're not friends.
你马上就会尝到大屌扇脸的滋味了
You're about to get dick-slapped.
我玩儿得超开心  你当时就这样
I had so much fun! You were like...
然后我就这样  你给我坐下  屎屌
And I was like, "Take a seat, shit dick."
就让我在平静中死去吧
Just let me die in peace.
我们会成为一个超棒的队伍
We make a great team!
噢天  我们不是一个队伍
Oh, God! We're not a team.
刚刚你为什么那么说  我们是朋友  搭档
Why'd you say that back there? We're friends, partners.
我们既不是朋友也不是搭档
We're not partners or friends.
这故事的结局可不是咱们迎着夕阳骑向远方
This doesn't end with us riding into the sunset.
故事的结局是我死于癌症
It ends with me dying of cancer...
而你获得冰盒本届最佳软柿子奖
and you winning the Ice Box award for softest mouth.
这世界上我只在乎一个人
There's only one person in this world
然而她已经死了
that I care about, and she's gone.
你想活下去吗
You wanna survive?
别再想着捅这里最壮的那家伙一刀
Stop trying to shank the biggest guys in here...
你要和他做朋友
and make friends with them.
要和别人交朋友
Make friends with someone.
除了我
Anyone but me.
甚至要和黑色提姆交朋友
Maybe even Black Tim.
还是黑伊万来着  我忘了
Black Evan, I don't know.
我就记得他是个非裔美国人
All I remember is he was African-American.
系统故障
System malfunctioning.
7号12号14号27号牢房
Cells 7, 12, 14, 27.
滚回你们的牢房去  你们这些肮脏的变种人  进去
Back in your cells, you filthy mutants! Get in there!
1号3号7号8号牢房
Cells 1, 3, 7, 8.
搜索中
Searching.
4号牢房
定位到04号牢房
Cell 04 located.
这门打不开啊
Door won't open!
他妈的给我跪下
On your fucking knees!
那是我们的牢房
That was our cell.
我做了什么能惹毛这个
What did I do to piss off a grumpy old fucker
带着一只冬兵手臂的老混蛋啊
with a Winter Soldier arm?
离我远点  孩子
Get away from me, kid!
听我的  走
Listen to me! Go!
你好  罗素
Hello, Russell.
你好啊  超能力
Hello, superpowers.
你谁啊
Who are you?
蝙蝠侠
I'm Batman.
这一下够猛的啊
Oh. That's got some zip.
别自责了  我都没办法弄死我自己
Don't feel bad. Even I can't kill me.
说话
Talk!
什么没骨气的人渣才会
What kind of spineless shit stick
试着去杀一个14岁的孩子啊
tries to kill a 14-year-old boy?
你可能现在就需要开始交代
You might wanna start talking!
因为在这种情况下真的开枪我也不是只干过一两次了
'Cause I got a long history of firing at times like this!
我叫电索
The name's Cable.
我来自未来  别多管闲事
I'm from the future. Just walk away.
所以你来自未来吗
So, you're from the future.
我有3个问题要问
I have three questions then.
一  回响贝斯还流行吗
One, is dubstep still a thing?
二  《龙卷鲨》系列出到几了
Two, which Sharknado are we on?
三  观众是什么才会说
And three, at what point do audiences say...
别再拍机械手臂了
"Enough with the robotic arms"?
回响贝斯是给娘炮听的
Dubstep's for pussies.
你人设太黑暗了
You're so dark!
你确定你不是从DC宇宙来的吗
Are you sure you're not from the DC universe?
我超爱回响贝斯的
I love dubstep!
那是个腰包吗
Is that a fanny pack?
我90年代也没有这玩意儿
I used to have one of those in 1990-never.
拿这个纪念你吧
Something to remember you by.
还给我  我一直随身带着的
Give me that back! That goes with me everywhere.
就像你那该死的腰包一样
Like the memory of your fucking fanny pack!
为什么你要保护那个孩子
Why are you protecting the kid?
我根本不在乎他好吧
I don't give a fuck about him...
还有他那个《你是我妈妈吗》的情结
and his Are You My Mother? Complex!
这个是干嘛的
What's this one do?
每部电影里  主角都有
In every film, there's a moment
跌到谷底的时刻
when the hero hits rock bottom.
在《冰上轻驰》里  是约翰·坎迪
In Cool Runnings, it was when John Candy's
最爱的雪橇坏掉的时候
prized bobsled broke.
在《人体蜈蚣》里  那就是那些人
In Human Centipede, it was when those people...
报名要拍那部电影的时候
signed on to be in that movie.
但在这个电影里
But in this film, well...
你正在看这一时刻呢
you're looking at it.
他妈的跪下  变种人
On your fucking knees, mutant.
谷
Rock...
底
meet bottom.
我爱你  韦德·威尔逊
I love you, Wade Wilson.
妮莎
Ness?
嘿  妮莎
Hey, Ness!
妮莎  你能让我进去吗
Ness, can you let me in?
求你了  求你了
Please! Please.
天啊
Jesus.
你没给我多少指示啊
You're not giving me a lot of direction here.
我走到山穷水尽了
I'm at the end of my rope.
然后我加入了X战警
Then I joined the X-Men.
我进了监狱  我
I went to prison. I, uh...
是那个孩子吗
Is it the kid?
孩子  他们给我们一个超越自己的机会
Kids give us a chance to be better than we used to be.
那个孩子
The kid!
这正是她的意思
That's exactly what she meant.
你的心需要在正确的地方
Your heart needs to be in the right place.
我不会抛弃这个孩子的
I'm not gonna abandon this kid.
从没有人照顾过他  从没
He's never had anyone, ever.
我需要无私一些
I need to be selfless.
是啊  但这是什么意思
Yeah, but what does that mean?
就是说我要去救罗素
It means I'm gonna save Russell.
也许我没能救凡妮莎
Maybe I couldn't save Vanessa...
但或许我可以救一个在有活力的新西兰青少年
but maybe I can save a robust teenager from New Zealand.
是啊  但我的意思是  这个词  无私
Yeah, but what I mean is, like, the world "selfless."
我真的不知道它什么意思
I literally don't know what that means.
天啊
Jesus Christ.
好吧  听着  据我的人说
Okay, look. According to my guy, okay...
这些变种人要被转移到
those muties are being transferred
120公里以外的超级监狱去
to a supermax, 80 miles away.
很好  那我半路劫狱就是了
Great, I'll pick 'em off along the way.
你先等下  兄弟  好吗
Hold your testicles there, buddy, okay?
我们面对的会是一支装甲护送队
We're talking about an armored convoy...
一个来自未来的邪恶超级战士
and a vicious super soldier from the future...
他想把你的头颅变成一个可操的烟灰缸
that is looking to turn your skull into a fuckable ashtray.
你知道我们需要什么吗
You know what we need to do?
我们需要建立一支队伍
We need to build a fucking team.
我们需要强壮的  道德上灵活的
We need 'em tough, morally flexible...
足够年轻的人  这样他们可以
and young enough so they can carry
再支撑这个系列10到12年
this franchise 10 to 12 years.
我的身体就是死亡的工具
My body is an instrument of death.
现在不行  都朋德
Not now, Dopinder.
我会有大用处的
I could be of great use.
你的超能力是什么
What's your superpower?
- 勇气  - 真可爱
- Courage. - That's adorable.
你有没有勇气去检查一下
Do you have the courage to check and see...
纸巾盒里餐巾纸还够不够了
if there are enough sanitary napkins in the dispenser?
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
我很抱歉你要看到这一幕
I'm sorry you had to see that,
不过我挺高兴你听到了
although I'm glad you heard it.
好吧  那我开始征集简历了
All right, I'll put out a call for resumes.
但我们不会给他们付医疗或者牙医保险的
But we're not paying medical or dental.
是时候重新登陆领英了
It's time to get back on Linkedln.
八点开始转移
Transport will begin at 0800 hours...
你他妈的想要什么
What the fuck do you want?
这他妈的是我的布丁
That's my fucking pudding.
- 去你妈的布丁吧  - 你喜欢布丁吗
- Fuck your pudding! - You like pudding?
有人吗
Hello?
我知道你在里面
I know you're in there.
在这里面做最强大的那个囚犯肯定很难
Must be hard being the biggest guy in here.
独孤求败  是吧
Lonely at the top, eh?
他们明天要转移我们了
They're moving us tomorrow.
或许我可以帮你从这里逃出去
Maybe I can get you out of here.
我们可以征服全世界
And we can make the whole world our bitch.
我们需要一个秘密代码
We need a secret code.
不  这太蠢了  罗素  白痴
No, that's stupid, Russell. Idiot.
我们是一队了
We're a team.
我们就像暴徒  我们就像黑帮
We're like thugs, we're like gangsters.
我就像图帕克  你就像艾斯·库珀
I'm like Tupac, and you're like Ice Cube.
据说  她还会说唱
Supposedly, she can rap, too.
我喜欢这个
I like that.
真棒  这些人都真棒
Terrific, these are all terrific.
这位是喧嚣
Meet Bedlam.
名字真酷  超能力是什么
Cool name! Superpowers?
我可以
I can distort
扭曲电场
electrical fields.
包括你们脑袋里的那个
Including the one inside your brain...
引起焦虑  疑惑
causing anxiety, confusion...
疼痛
pain.
所以  你基本上就是达沃·马修斯
So, basically, you're Dave Matthews.
我们可以用上他
We can use him.
我是时代精神
I'm Zeitgeist.
酷  我喜欢这名字
Cool. I like it.
所以你的超能力是
So you have the power
把握社会的脉搏吗
to put your finger on the pulse of society?
不
No.
不  我可以吐酸性呕吐物
No, I spit acidic vomit.
你想要我
Do you want me
- 展示一下吗  - 不
- to demonstrate? - No!
我们相信你的话
We'll take your word for it.
谢谢你  好的  听着  我们都吃过阿比汉堡  好吧
Thank you. Yeah. Listen, we've all eaten at Arby's, okay?
这位是消影人
And this is the Vanisher.
但
But...
消影人
Vanisher!
- 棒  - 是吧
- Nice! - Right?
他不在这儿  在吗
He's not here, is he?
他可能是迟到了
He may be running late.
我的名字是生锈  但我自称碎星
My name's Rusty, but I go by Shatterstar.
这不错  是的
That's good, yeah.
- 生锈太难听了  - 不好听
- "Rusty" is terrible. - Toughie.
- 所以你来自哪里  - 莫焦世界星球
- So, uh, where are you from? - The planet Mojo World.
- 所以你就是个外星人了  - 不好听的名字
- So you're an alien, I guess. - Bad name.
这可以怎么  帮到我们呢
How does that, uh, help us?
我基本上在任何一件事情上都比你们强
I'm basically better than you at everything.
我一定要找到一个星球
Just once, I'm gonna find a planet of people
上面的人什么都比我差
that are worse than me at everything.
一大群脑残
A whole bunch of functional idiots.
我到那里  就会是他们的超人了
I'm gonna go there, and I'm gonna be their Superman.
加拿大不就是
Isn't that Canada?
你可闭嘴吧
You shut your goddamn trash mouth!
- 见见  - 多米诺
- Meet... - Domino.
- 你的超能力是什么  - 我运气好
- What's your shtick? - I'm lucky.
如果你运气那么好  你和我们共事做什么
If you're so lucky, then what are you doing here with us?
我还不知道呢
I don't know yet.
这话是什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
就是我还不知道呢
It means that I don't know yet.
但我在这儿肯定是有原因的
But there's a reason why I'm here,
等我知道了我自然就明白了
and I'll know when I know.
一般来说  我做什么事都很顺利的
Everything usually works out for me.
运气可不是超能力
Luck isn't a superpower.
- 是的  它是  - 不  它不是
- Yes, it is. - No, it isn't.
- 是的  它是  - 不是  女士
- Yes, it is. - No, ma'am.
马里奥·不是-佩斯
Mario No-pez.
- 是的  - 纳乔奶酪
- Yeah. - Nacho cheese.
不  它一定是  我真的
No, it definitely is. I really...
它绝不可能是
There's no way that it...
抱歉  我打断了你
Sorry, I was interrupting you.
- 抱歉  是  我打断了你  - 不  不  不  你可以先说
- Sorry. No, I interrupted you. - No, no, no. You can go first.
我只是打算接着说  不  它不是
Oh, I was just gonna say, "No, it isn't."
我也就打算说回去  然后说  是的  它是
I was gonna just bring it back to that yes, it is.
那我们折个中  说  不  它不是
Let's meet in the middle and say, "No, it isn't."
- 但它是  - 好吧
- But it is. - Okay.
- 你被录用了  - 你被录用了
- You're hired! - You're hired.
我真幸运
Oh, lucky me.
她真棒
She's great.
最后  但并非最不重要的
And last, but not least...
彼得
Peter.
这是照骗吗还是咋
Am I getting catfished here or...?
你有什么超能力想告诉我们吗
Any powers you wanna tell us about?
没有
No.
我没有
I don't have one.
我就是看到了广告然后觉得挺有趣的
Um, I just saw the ad and thought it looked fun.
你入选了
You're in.
- 好的  - 干
- Yeah. - Fuck!
真是令人满意的工作
It's fulfilling work.
我们走
Let's go!
这里是17护送队  正在离开冰盒
This is Convoy 17 departing the Ice Box.
我们在路上了
We are en route.
和平使人变得软弱
Peacetime makes people soft.
我出生于战争中
I was born into war.
在战争中长大
Bred into it.
好吧
Okay.
人们以为他们了解疼痛
People think they understand pain.
你经历过的最疼的疼痛是什么
What's the most pain you've ever felt?
你把我绑的就挺
These restraints are pretty...
我有一个单子
I've got a list.
我们来一起过一遍吧
We're gonna work down it.
一起
Together.
第一项  我要掰弯某个东西
Number one, I'm gonna bend something.
某个并不应该被掰弯的东西
Something that was not meant to bend.
我要在这里打断你了
I'm gonna stop you right there
因为我撑不到第二项
because I'm not gonna make it to two.
我甚至撑不到第一项
I won't even make it to one.
我可不太能接受疼痛  你懂吧
I don't do well with pain, you know.
如果我踩到了脚趾  那我今天就啥也不干了
If I stub my toe, I'm done for the day.
他们砍掉《大学生费莉希蒂》时  我都哭了
I cried when they canceled Felicity.
当我害怕的时候  我会紧张性勃起
When I get really scared, I get nervous erections.
我现在就是
I have one right now.
别看  只会让它更糟
Don't look. It'll only make it worse.
我不想让你伤到我
I don't want you to hurt me,
我会告诉你  你想知道的一切
and I'll tell you anything you wanna know.
除了他们在那儿
Except for where they are.
罗素在一支沿格里杜根公园大道
Russell's in a convoy heading southbound
南行的护送队里
on Gerry Duggan Parkway.
那个怪物和他在一起  我不会招惹他的
The monster's with them. I wouldn't fuck with him.
你们都知道计划了
You all know the plan.
拦截车队
Intercept the convoy,
救命
抓住那个男孩  不是那种不恰当的方式
grab the boy. But not inappropriately!
你知道不
You know what,
我也不会招惹死侍的
I wouldn't fuck with Deadpool either.
因为他组建了一个团队  他势不可挡
Because he's built a team. He's unstoppable.
他屁股里有根笔  他会用那个玩意捅你
He has an ass pen. He'll stab you with it.
注意电索这个小矮人
Watch out for this guy, Cable!
他180厘米左右  没有漫画里那么高
He's very short, 5'11". Not like in the comics.
如果我们成功了  就能早早回家
And if we succeed, we all go home early.
如果你要去找他们  电索  我警告你
So if you go after them, Cable, I warn you...
天气预报说有大风
there's a wind advisory in effect.
空中有乱流
A little turbulent up here.
我虽然对电索了解得不多
I don't know much about this Cable fella...
但我敢保证他杀的人绝对没有
but I guarantee he hasn't killed
黑色素瘤杀死的人多
as many people as melanoma has.
我们马上到
We're getting close!
最为一个前X战警
As a former X-Man...
- 学员  - 我谢你啊  喧嚣
- Trainee. - Thank you, Bedlam.
我对一个队伍名字居然公然表明性别歧视
I was always appalled by the blatant sexism
感到震惊
in the group's name.
男性X战警  男战警
X-Men! Men!
我想说的是  我们队伍将会有进步性思维
The point is, our group will be forward thinking.
一定要性别平等
Gender neutral.
从现在开始  我们就叫
From now on, we'll be known as...
X特攻队
X-Force.
这名字有点像前一个名字派生的
Isn't that a little derivative?
我不记得征求过你的意见  彼得
I don't recall asking your opinion, Peter!
那不是我说的
That wasn't me.
直升机悬停在400米左右的高度
Hang the laundry out at 1,300 feet...
拦截运输车  抓走那个男孩
intercept the convoy, and grab the boy.
杀戮时间到
Let's bring on the carnage, baby!
等下了直升机  让你们见识一下我的能耐
Get me on the ground, watch me go!
耶
Yeah!
我等不及要杀人了
I can't wait to kill!
等一下
Hey! Hey! Hey!
我只想说我为咱们这支队伍感到骄傲
I just wanna say how proud I am of this team.
你们看起来棒极了
You know, you guys look amazing!
消影?  我相信你看起来也棒极了
Vanisher, I have no doubt you look amazing too.
这是一支
This is the family
我一直做梦都想拥有的大家庭
that I've always dreamed of having and I...
见鬼
Ah, shit.
我只是偶尔会噎住
I just get a little choked up sometimes.
我打断一下  这么大的风
I hate to interrupt, but is anybody nervous
你们不紧张吗
about the high winds?
- 加里  - 我叫彼得
- Gary. - My name's Peter.
我知道这是你第一次  不过放轻松
I realize that you're new to this, but relax.
你被大能者选中了
You've been chosen by a higher power.
- 他刚才是不是称自己为神  - 我觉得是的
- Did he just call himself God? - I think he did.
- 我想回家  - 我还想让麦当劳
- I'd like to go home. - And I'd like...
全年都卖烤汁猪排堡呢
the McRib to be available year round,
但有时候梦想不会实现
but sometimes dreams don't come true.
我在特种部队待了10年
I spent 10 years in Special Forces.
你觉得因为一点小风我们就不用
You think we didn't jump out of the plane
跳出飞机了吗
because of a light breeze?
你现在就面临这样的处境  小胡子
You're in this shit now, Mustache!
我朝你吼只是想激励其他人
I'm only yelling to impress the other guys.
我不会让你出事的  小熊甜心
I'd never let anything happen to you, Sugarbear.
莱纳德  开舱门
Leonard, hit it!
跳跳跳
Go! Go! Go!
战个痛快
Let's get some!
爽翻了
Oh, yeah!
运输车  12点钟方向  听我命令
Convoy, 12 o'clock! On my command!
- 开伞  - 哦  现在哦
- Deploy! - Oh, hey now!
妈呀
Whoa!
有点跑偏了
Little off course here.
我去他亲娘的腿
Holy mommy fucking shit!
他们在那呢
Ah, there they are.
看这群小可爱
Look at these gorgeous sons of bitches.
没错  就这样  喧嚣
Oh, yeah! That's right, Bedlam!
不是吧  我了个大鸡巴操
No! Tripping motherfucking billies!
碎星  你可以的
Shatterstar. Okay, you got this.
往左
Left!
是舞台的左边  你个傻逼
No, stage left, you idiot!
好吧  我看是找到了
Well, I guess we found something
你不擅长的东西了
you're not better at.
消影?
Vanisher.
也许风不会吹它看不见的东西吧
Maybe the wind can't blow what it can't see.
有没有搞错
Oh! Really?
好吧  四个人也是可以的
All right, we could do this with four.
小熊甜心  干得漂亮伙计
Sugarbear. You got this, buddy!
就是这样  这就是X特攻队精神
That's the stuff! That's the X-Force spirit!
绝对不要低估一个留胡子的男人的能力
Never underestimate a man with a mustache!
布鲁克林随便问一个人都能知道答案
Just ask anyone in Brooklyn.
我们做到了
We did it!
你他妈是个超级英雄  你
You're a goddamn superhero, you!
X特攻队
X-Force!
X-Force.
哦
Oh!
彼得
Peter.
我抓住你了伙计
I got you, buddy!
- 你会没事的  - 这看起来不妙啊
- You're gonna be fine! - This is not good, man!
你可以的大块头  加把劲  彼得
You got this, big guy! Here we go, Peter!
看着我  我们是X特攻队
Look at me. We're X-Force, right?
- 对  我们是X特攻队  - 我们是X特攻队
- Yeah, we're X-Force. - We're X-Force.
我的天  什么鬼玩意
Oh, my God! What the fuck?
他妈的酸性呕吐物
Fucking acidic vomit!
天啊  我快吐我面罩里了
Oh, God! I'm gonna throw up in my mask.
我在运输车上面
Okay, I'm over the convoy.
剩下的队员落哪了
Where did the rest of the team land?
有好消息也有坏消息
Good news and bad news.
坏消息是整个团队死完了
Bad news is the whole team is dead.
好消息是
The good news is,
我觉得没人会想念碎星
I don't think anyone's gonna miss Shatterstar.
他可是个刺头  但是保罗
He was a bit of a prick. Oh, but Paul!
是彼得
Peter!
彼得  我会非常想他的
Peter, I'm gonna miss him most.
不过消影?有可能
But there is a slight chance
能挺过来
Vanisher could make it.
好吧  没机会了  他挂了
Nope, no chance. He's dead.
整个团队
The whole team?
只是主要的  我们还活着呢
Only the main ones. We're still good.
去你的  蠢货
Fuck, you are dumb.
就算发生了这一切  我还是忍不住说
Even after all this time, I still can't talk about it.
谁他妈知道风这么大
Who knew these winds would be so strong?
每个人  直升机里的和直升机外边的
Everyone! Everyone on the helicopter!
每个人都知道风大
And everyone not on the helicopter!
他们进隧道了
They're headed into the tunnel.
我是那个孩子的唯一希望了
I'm that kid's only hope,
等着听我的命令
so sit tight and wait for my word.
随便吧
Whatever.
我们要跟丢了  我要降落了
We're gonna lose 'em. I'm dropping in.
不能这么做  唯一的幸存者
Uh, that's a negative, sole survivor.
运气可不是超级能力  我们完蛋了
Luck is not a superpower! We are so fucked!
不  我们绝对没完蛋
No, we most certainly are not fucked.
讲真  我没理解
Seriously, I don't get it!
你的眼睛能发射幸运光线
What, you shoot luck lasers out of your eyes?
这个画面很难想象
It's just it's hard to picture.
而且也不太好电影化
And certainly not very cinematic.
运气
I mean, luck?
是哪个嗑嗨了的  戴着玻璃吸管的
What coked out, glass pipe-sucking
变态漫画家
freakshow comic book artist...
想出了这么个东西
came up with that little chestnut?
那家伙估计也不会画脚吧
Probably a guy who can't draw feet!
作者Liefeld真的不会画脚
再一次  拯救世界的使命落在了我的肩上
Once again, it all falls on my shoulders.
这就是为什么注定这个电影只有我这么一个主角
It's why I'm cursed to be a solo act.
- 在大地上漫步  - 我进来了
- Wander the Earth... - I'm in.
抱歉你说什么
I'm sorry, what did you say?
我进来了
I'm in.
你他妈是怎么进去的
How in the fuck are you in already?
哦  惨了
Oh, shit.
电索  12点钟方向
It's Cable. 12 o'clock.
好嘞
Okay.
新计划  运用你所有想象出来的能力
New plan. Use all of your imaginary powers
来阻止电索杀了那个孩子
to stop Cable from killing that kid.
我从你后边赶过来
I'm coming up on your six.
那把枪碉堡了
That gun is amazing!
嘿  混蛋
Hey! Asshole!
他在哪  我看不到他
Where is he? I can't see him.
他在你上面
He's on top of you.
他从后面进去了
He's going in through the back!
天啊  他进去了
Oh, God, he's inside!
你能听见你自己说的什么吧
You hear yourself, right?
这个双关是个意外
Accidental double entendres!
罗素  罗素·柯林斯
Russell! Russell Collins!
别碰那个孩子  约翰·康纳
Hands off that kid, John Connor!
详见《终结者》
不要啊
No, no, no!
见鬼了
Shit!
两个人的游戏
Two can play that game!
抓住了  好吧  并没有
Got it! No, I don't.
你的表演时刻
Showtime, mama!
幸运女神  你来开车
Lady Luck, take the wheel.
我想问问你是谁  不过反正你快要死了
I'd ask who you are, but you'll be dead in a second.
我叫多?诺  而且很怀疑
I'm Domino, and doubtful.
撑住啊  阿多
Hang in there, Doms!
这么开车好难啊
Oh, this is really hard.
把我的木滚球游戏币还给我
And give me back my Skee-Ball token.
- 你干的不错啊  - X特攻队
- You're doing great. - X-Force.
看来回响贝斯永不死
I guess dubstep never dies.
你杀了?色汤姆  你这个种族歧视的变态
You killed Black Tom, you racist son of a bitch!
这真不幸
That's unfortunate.
我们刹车坏了
We got no brakes!
自己想办法
Figure it out!
还没有我杀不死的人
There's nothing I can't kill.
有人会空手道嘛
Somebody knows karate.
来噻  开枪打我噻  独眼威利
Give me your best shot, One-Eyed Willy.
疼
Ow.
搞起
Here we go.
多?诺  介不介意把车慢下来
Domino, mind slowing us down?
孤注一掷了
Here goes nothing.
咚咚
Knock, knock.
这才是我的好孩子
That's my boy.
我了个
Holy...
我首先承认
I'll be first to admit...
这可没按计划走啊
this did not go according to plan.
我还要第一个承认
I'll also be the first to admit that
这个计划是用蜡笔画的
that plan was written in crayon.
罗素找了新闺蜜  小杰
Looks like Russell found a new friend. Jelly.
多米诺还有点厉害
Turns out Domino's a bit of a badass,
幸运  可能有那么一点点
and maybe, possibly mildly lucky.
电索的话  心情好像不太好
But Cable? Ugh. That guy's in a mood.
马上  他心情
A mood that is
就要跌倒谷底了
about to get significantly worse.
怎么  怎么感觉不大对劲
Something is so terribly, terribly wrong.
妈妈我好痛
Oh, God, that hurt.
罗素
Russell.
Russell!
罗素  你哪呢
Russ, where are ya?
罗素  罗素  你没事
Russell. Russell, you're okay!
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God. Oh, my God!
红坦克
Juggernaut!
就说好像看到你了
I thought that was you!
早知道穿白裤子了
I should've worn my white pants.
你可能都听烦了  不过我是你的大粉丝
You probably get this a lot, but I am a huge fan.
非凡X战警183期  雷神411期
Uncanny X-Men 183. Thor 411.
无限X战警12期
X-Men Unlimited 12.
我做梦都想
You know, it has always been a dream of mine...
看着你杀气腾腾走过来
to see my face reflected in your helmet...
头盔上倒映着我的帅脸
as you charge at me with murderous intent.
我不是说现在
I don't mean right now.
我要把你撕成两半
I'm gonna rip you in half now.
这真是红坦克会说的话
That is such a Juggernaut thing to say.
我的天哪  感觉不到腿了
Oh, my God! I can't feel my legs.
腿呢
I can't feel...
哦  这那
Oh, no, they're right here.
罗素  拉我一把啊
Got 'em. God, Russell.
我有任务要做
I have a mission.
我要去复仇
To get my revenge.
我要去烧死校长
I'm going to burn that headmaster alive.
你不适合复仇
You're not the revenge type.
听朋友一句劝
Take it from a friend.
朋友  是你有病了  我保护的你
Friend? You were sick, and I protected you.
你自己也说了
You said it yourself.
我不是你朋友  去找个更牛的吧
"I'm not your friend. Find someone stronger."
我听你的了
So I did.
罗素  我当时没能力保护你
Russell, I couldn't protect you back then.
但我现在有了  你还想要我怎样
But I can now. What do you want me to say, huh?
说我在乎你吗  妈的
"I care about you"? 'Cause goddamn it,
我是真在乎你  罗素
I care about you, Russell.
我比红坦克差啥啦
What's Juggernaut got that I don't have?
你敢说是腿  我知道你要说是腿
Don't you say legs! I know you're gonna say legs!
- 腿呗  - 扎铁了
- Legs! - Still hurts to hear out loud!
干啥干啥  你拉毛线啊拉
What is that? That's not a real rope!
给我回来  小兔崽子
You get back here, young man!
阿多
Doms!
小多  求你拉俺一把
Doms, get me out of here, please.
把把我胳膊当书包背
Use my arms as backpack straps.
老天爷让你过来
I think we may have found
估计就是干这个的吧
your cosmic reason for being here.
我很确定不是
I'm pretty sure this isn't it.
X特攻队
X-Force.
孩子小还有救
No child is hopeless.
你别放弃啊
Don't give up on the boy.
他怎么走的那么爽快
How could he just walk away?
他眼神那么冷漠
It was the coldness in his eyes.
你要是能听到就好了
You should've heard it.
家庭真的是屁
I guess family really is an F-word.
帮我揉揉腿呗  妈妈
Rub my legs, Mama.
干啥子
Why would I rub your legs?
不嘛  宝宝腿疼  我在长个呢
Please, they hurt. I have growing pains.
咋回事
What in the...
你手怎么又小了
Why is your hand so tiny again?
那不是我的手
That's not my hand.
有句mmp不知当讲不当讲
Oh! Mary, mother of Joseph!
其实有点爽
That was nice for me.
韦德  我听说护送队的事了
Wade! I heard what happened with the convoy and...
你咋不穿裤子咧
Why wouldn't you cover that up?
勇士无所不惧
A warrior has nothing to be ashamed of.
你还是惧一下吧  瞅瞅你
Yeah, but you do. Look at you.
你穿的这是齐逼小短衫
You're just straight shirt-cocking it,
学小孩露屁股啊
toddler-style.
猜对了  我这是小熊维尼风
Oh, yeah. Full Winnie the Pooh.
到底咋回事  给老娘说说
The hell's happening? Describe it.
还是别问了吧
I wouldn't ask him to do that, if I were you.
- 就是  - 说吧
- It's like, um... - Here we go.
就好像他屁眼里拉小孩
It's like he was giving birth anally,
拉到一半放弃了
but they quit halfway through.
腿拽出来了
They got the legs out, and they said,
然后大夫甩手走人了
"You know what, I'm done."
开心吗
Happy?
好像是腰以下都是木偶
It's like he's a Muppet from the waist down.
但这一回  你能看见
But this time, you can see
木偶的屌
the Muppet's dick.
格罗弗丁丁就一根小树枝长
Grover's got a cock the size of a twig.
黄鼠狼先生  我不能再停马路中间了
Mr. Weasel, I can no longer be double-parked.
已经被罚三次了
I've had three tickets already.
艾玛不是吧  死哥  又这样婶的了
No, no, no, DP, not again!
这还不是第一回么
This has happened before?
老弟  要不要吐啊这是
Jesus! Either vomit or don't.
看你选择困难症  我想屎
The indecision is killing me.
为什么上帝不带走我的听觉
Why couldn't God take my hearing?
嘴合上呗  我在长个呢
Cool your pits. They're growing back.
我的是你老脸
I'm talking about your face.
还是第一回看你摘面具
I've never seen you without your mask before.
- 吓死宝宝了  - 跟牛油果似的
- Jesus Christ! - Looks like an avocado.
你的腿倒是挺可爱
Your legs, though, they're cute.
借你条裤子啊
You wanna borrow a pair of pants?
谢谢大家都来看我
I'm glad everybody dropped by.
你肯定好奇我为啥没联系你们吧
You must be wondering why I didn't call you here.
告诉你我来干啥
I'll tell you why I'm here.
时间旅行者的妻子的丈夫
"The Time Traveler's Wife's" husband...
差点把我打洗
beat me within an inch of my life.
还折磨我
He was torturing me!
但我只是把他要听的都告诉他了
But all I told him was everything he wanted to know.
所以我来这里给大家准备武器
So, I'm here to help us gear up.
这样你们就可以替我去打洗他
So we can go after him without me.
不行
No!
我一个人就行
I'm doing this alone.
红坦克
The Juggernaut
- 会把你们都灭了的  - 有道理
- will kill you all. - Fair enough.
等我几个小时
I just need a couple of hours to get some legs
- 长长个  - 你要怎么做
- under me. - What will you do?
那孩子怎么对我我都不在乎
I don't care what the kid did to me.
我不能让电索抓到他
I ain't letting Cable get to him,
淹死他我也认了
even if I have to teabag him to death.
现在你也就能让他呛口水
It's really just a sip of tea at this point.
能比上嘴不  黑黑寡妇  我还妹说完呢
Zip it, black Black Widow! I'm flowing.
首先要做的
The first order of business is
就是带我去找电索
to get me in front of Cable...
这样我就把他吸干
so I can pull all the fucking blood out of his body...
抽出骨头来装点节日
and fashion his bones into holiday jewelry.
然后拨他的皮
Then, I'm gonna take his skin...
拿来做撩妹用的鼓
and stretch it out over a homemade mating drum.
他就站你们后面  是吧
He's standing right behind you, isn't he?
什么他妈的鬼
What in the ass?
这里是上陌陌打广告了  还是探探啊
Is this apartment listed on Tinder? Grindr?
你搞错地方了  未来男孩
You picked the wrong shithole to fuck, future boy.
有必要这样吗
Ugh. Is that really necessary?
不是  这是他的《本能》
No. It's his "Basic Instinct."
详见《本能》
有何贵干啊
What can we help you with?
我是来提议[求欢]的
I'm here to proposition you.
哎哟哟
Oh, boy!
他还面不改色的
He's really teeing it up, isn't he?
谁先讲这个笑话
Who gets to make the first joke?
一起吧
I think we should all do it at the same time.
赞
Good call.
只需要45美金  我就给你口一个
For $45, you get sucky-suck.
但是必须隔着裤子  你懂的
I only do over the pants, mouth stuff.
卧槽
Fuck!
盖·皮尔斯演的
The Proposition has a wonderful
《关键协议》可好了
Guy Pearce performance.
等下等下  我重说
Wait, wait, wait! I wanna do mine over.
- 你再说下台词呗  - 我需要帮忙
- Give us the line again. - I need your help!
我比你还更不愿意合作  知道不
Trust me, I'm even less happy about this than you are...
可是你释放了红坦克  大撒比
but you unleashed the Juggernaut, you dumb cunt!
我一个人打不过他
I can't bring him down alone.
所以就来了
So here we are.
可是现在X特攻队
We're no longer accepting applications
不招人了  很不幸
for X-Force, unfortunately.
就算我们招人
Even if we were...
天气预报说有大风  一直持续到
there's a wind advisory in effect until at least...
时间不多了
We don't have a lot of time.
你朋友马上要杀第一个人了
Your friend's about to make his first kill.
老哥  你要是这么懂
No offense, but if you know so much...
那你咋不穿梭回去  把他扼杀在摇篮里
why not travel back to when he was a baby, kill him then?
还可以做件好事  再往回走走
Or better yet, head back a little further,
把希特勒扼杀在襁褓里
kill baby Hitler.
我是用机器穿越时空
I use a device to slide through time.
但是穿的时间越多  就越难控制
The longer I travel, the harder it is to control.
我有两个电池  一个带我到这里
I've got two charges, one to get me here,
一个带我回家
one to get me home.
诶
Well.
这编剧真懒
That's just lazy writing.
你的小朋友今晚
Your boy's gonna kill the headmaster
会杀死校长
of the orphanage tonight.
之后  他就爱上了这个味道
After that, he gets a real taste for it.
就像十岁的克斯汀·邓斯特  傻逼
Like 10-year-old Kirsten Dunst, motherfucker!
之后他会不断地
So he keeps killing...
杀啊杀啊
and killing, and killing,
杀人如麻
and killing.
直到有一天  他杀错了人
Until one day, he kills the wrong fucking people.
杀了我的人
My people.
淡定点
Relax.
我就想从工具包里掏点东西
I'm retrieving something from my utility bag.
这玩意是腰包好伐
It's a goddamn fanny pack...
你不可能不知道  大撒比
and you know it, you sick son of a bitch!
明明区别那么明显
The difference is night and day.
看到你我想起了老婆
You remind me of my wife.
说啥
I'm sorry.
我说  看到你我想起了老婆
I said, "You remind me of my wife."
我不爽的是  你一边说这话
No, I'm sorry that you said that...
还一边看着我  还一边擦唇膏
while making heavy eye contact and applying lip balm.
她总是在挣扎
She always struggled.
但她很幽默
But she was funny...
把她的痛苦都加上了幽默的滤镜
and filtered her pain through the prism of humor.
这个我怎么也学不会
Something I could never master.
她去世是我的错
It was my fault she died.
阻止他那样的人是我的工作
It was my job to stop people like him.
好几次我很接近了
I came close a few times.
他并不高兴
He wasn't too happy about that.
他想伤害我
He was trying to hurt me...
而且他知道怎么做
and he knew exactly how to do it.
愿上帝保佑
Blessed are the wicked
经我手治愈之恶人
who are healed by my hand.
他来我的家
He came into my home...
然后夺走了唯一使之成为家的东西
and took the only thing that made it a home.
耳熟吧
Sound familiar?
- 我很难过  - 算了
- I'm sorry. - Uh-huh.
不是  我真的很难过
No, I'm really sorry.
但那不是罗素
But that isn't Russell.
- 并不一定要是他  - 如果你知道我知道的事情
- It doesn't have to be him. - If you knew what I knew...
是  他控制不了自己的愤怒
Yeah, he's got anger issues...
也许有点点学习障碍
maybe a small learning disability...
一丢丢糖尿病
splash of diabetes...
但是都能治好
but nothing that can't be fixed.
如果你能回去
If you could go back...
阻止杀死你妹子的人  你愿意吗
and stop the people that took your girl, would you?
我他妈当然愿意
Of course I fucking would!
但我不会杀一个小孩
But I wouldn't kill a kid.
我不是让你杀小孩
I'm not asking you to kill a kid!
我杀那个小孩
I'll kill the kid.
我是请求你拯救上百个其他的小孩
I'm asking you to save hundreds of other kids.
罗素会烧毁那个孤儿院
Russell's gonna burn down that orphanage.
而我猜你死掉的女朋友
And I can imagine your dead girlfriend...
会想让你做正确的事  不是吗
would want you to do the right thing, wouldn't she?
所以怎么说  帅哥
So, what's it gonna be, handsome?
给我一个救他的机会
Give me a chance to save him.
- 什么  - 你说
- What? - You said...
他一旦杀死一个人  就会爱上这个味道
once he kills someone, he gets a taste for it.
如果我们能在此之前找到他
If we can get to him before that happens...
向我保证你会给我一个机会
promise you'll give me a chance
让他走上一条不同的路
to put him on a different path.
你怎么定义机会
Define "chance."
我也不知道  拯救一个人的灵魂
I don't know. How long does it take
要多长时间  这事不能
to save someone's soul? That's not...
我给你三十秒
I'll give you 30 seconds.
- 什么  不行  - 我能做到的最好了
- What? No! - Best I can do.
要不要随你
Take it or leave it.
他要走路了
He's doing it!
看这个小家伙  他要走路了
Look at the little fella. He's doing it.
他过来了
There he goes.
老天哪
Jesus Christ!
就上衣盖屌
Just shirt-cocking it.
呃
Ugh.
来来小家伙
There you go, little fella.
接着走  你会走路了
Go on, you're doing it!
我这漂亮的  没毛的  腿像扭扭糖的小宝贝
My beautiful, hairless, Twizzler-legged baby boy.
天
Christ!
真难看
That's disturbing.
三十秒
30 seconds.
- 说定  - 说定
- Deal. - Deal.
我完全不知道发生了什么
I have no idea what's happening.
这样其实最好
Probably for the best.
这就是为什么你永远不要生吃海星
And that is why you never eat a raw starfish.
这都是常识
It's just common sense.
我们去哪啊
Where the hell are we going?
你自己说的
You said it yourself.
谁也挡不住红坦克  我们需要后援
Nothing can stop the Juggernaut. We need backup.
我要用你的敌人的鲜血沐浴
I will bathe in the blood of your enemies.
你能把音乐关掉吗
Can you turn off the music?
你不必这样做
You'll do no such thing.
你干嘛不直接用印度口音说
Why don't you just say it in an Indian accent?
你他妈在
What the hell are you...?
又一次  偏见抬起了它丑陋的头
Once again, intolerance rears its ugly head.
我真抱歉  会变好的
I am so sorry. It gets better.
我不是种族歧视  智障
I'm not a fucking racist, moron!
这话你跟黑色汤姆说去  他就像我哥哥
Tell that to Black Tom. He was like a brother to me.
这事我赞成这个老白人
I'm with the old white guy on this one.
真是个转折
And that's a twist.
所以你在未来
So what exactly do you
具体做啥的啊
do in the future, anyway, huh?
某种士兵吗
Some kind of soldier?
嗯  差不多
Yeah, something like that.
我也当过兵  特种部队
I was a soldier. Special Forces.
我估计五十年后  我们会是好朋友
I bet 50 years from now, we're bestest buddies.
五十年后  你早死了
50 years from now, you're very dead.
你们这代人把地球搞昏迷了
Your entire generation fucked this planet into a coma.
砰
Boom!
剧透预警
Spoiler alert.
星球啊
Planets.
下一次绝对叫优步
Next time, Uber.
再给你剧个透
Here's a spoiler alert.
你不是英雄
You're not a fucking hero.
你只是个烦人的小丑  穿成一个性爱玩具
You're just an annoying clown dressed up as a sex toy.
我告诉你件事
Well, I got news for you.
我的心在正确的地方
My heart is in the right place.
罗素不会杀任何人
Russell's not gonna kill anyone.
因为我  他会知道真爱是什么样子
Because of me, he's gonna know what real love looks like.
因为你  我永远会知道
Because of you, I'll always know
一个有着小孩蛋蛋的成年人什么样子
what a grown man with baby balls looks like.
我长个  不乱给人看
I'm a grower, not a shower.
我应该上完大学的
I should've finished college.
就在这里
Right here!
我会犯错
I made mistakes!
我想弥补
I wanna take them back!
你信任我  我把这份信任
You trusted me. I took that trust...
变成了一个寻欢洞
and turned it into a glory hole
在那个机场厕所
in an airport bathroom.
明尼阿波利斯那个  你知道的
The one in Minneapolis. You know the one.
钢力士
Colossus!
如果不关乎生死我也不会找你帮忙
I wouldn't ask for your help unless it was life or death!
那个孩子需要我们帮助
That kid needs our help!
我知道你在听
I know you're listening!
他和红坦克组队了
He's teamed up with the Juggernaut!
红坦克啊
The Juggernaut!
那应该是我最喜欢的漫威角色
That's like my favorite Marvel character ever,
但你永远不应该见到自己的英雄
but you should never meet your heroes...
因为  说实话  他就是个屌人
because, honestly, he's a bit of a dick!
而像很多的屌一样  他硬得像个石头
And like a lot of dicks, he's as hard as a rock...
而且只会惹麻烦
and causes nothing but problems!
- 嗨韦德  - 嗨雪绪
- Hi, Wade! - Hi, Yukio!
请别
Please don't.
你们俩真有爱
You guys make a super cute couple.
嗯  我说哪了  哦对
Yeah. Where was I? Oh, yeah!
钢力士  我知道  我不配
Colossus! Look, I don't deserve
你的友谊  或者帮助
your friendship or your help.
但那个孩子配
But this kid does.
我不会像别人一样抛弃他
And I'm not gonna bail on him like everyone else.
得了吧
Oh, come on!
鸽子翅能来么
Any chance Pigeon Wings is available?
行吧  行吧
That's just fine! That's fine!
不行  你猜怎么
No! You know what?
做正确的事有时很糟
Doing the right thing is sometimes messy...
很操蛋  也不一定很方便
and fucked up, and not particularly convenient!
所以你就待在这个处男城堡吧
So stay here in Chateau de Virgin...
我们去干架了
while we go get our fuck on!
你做的不错
You're doing great.
所以你戴着个头盔
So you wear that helmet because
是因为你哥哥想读你的心
your brother tries to read your mind?
嗯不过他坐轮椅  所以平了
Yeah, but he's in a wheelchair, so even-steven.
有人来了  是罗素  先生
Someone's coming. It's Russell, sir.
他不是一个人
He's not alone.
看好孩子
Secure the children.
咱们去好好折腾一番如何
What do you say we go fuck some shit up?
“咱们好好折腾一番”是我身份证上的中间名
"Let's fuck some shit up" is my legal middle name.
给我殿后  我去找那个老头
Watch my back. I've got the old man.
好嘞  兄弟
Amen, brother.
该去创造奇迹了
Time to make the chimichangas.
三十秒
30 seconds.
我终于知道我为什么在这里了
I finally know why I'm here.
我在这里被抚养大的
I was raised in this place.
不是抚养  是折磨
Well, not raised. I was tortured.
哇  这是宇宙给你来这里的原因
Wow! It's your cosmic reason for being here.
- 走吗  - 会很好玩的
- Shall we? - This is gonna be fun.
嗯
Yeah!
喂  一直想问你
Hey! Been meaning to ask you...
这个诡异的  肮脏的流浪熊是啥
what's with the creepy, dirty hobo bear?
那不是脏  那是我死去女儿的血
It's not dirt. It's the blood of my dead daughter.
我对麸质过敏
I have a gluten sensitivity.
所以喝一杯红酒  我就
So one glass of wine, I just...
嗯
Yeah.
真希望我们能穿越到过去
Wish we could head back in time,
我可以收回那些话
and I could take all that back.
咱们就放音乐吧
We should just cue the music.
欢迎回家  罗素  我们很想你
Welcome home, Russell. We missed you.
罗素
Russell!
你不需要这样做  咱们谈谈吧
You don't need to do this! Let's talk!
你怎么穿得像大学炸弹客一样
Why are you dressed like the Unabomber?
这就是为什么
That's why!
告诉你这个小傻逼偏离太远了
Told you this little fucker's too far gone.
闭嘴  灭霸  我们有言在先  你个
Zip it, Thanos! We have a deal and you fuck...
喂
Hey!
我要把那个出租车司机塞你屁眼里
I'm gonna shove that cab driver right up your ass.
我的身体和手都好软
My body and my hands are so soft.
你还是回车里比较好
You should probably head back to the car.
我觉得我还是回车里了
I think I'll head back to the car.
你开枪效果最好
It works best when you pull the trigger.
这枪真棒
That gun is amazing!
说啊
Say it!
你就是个怪物
You are an abomination!
现在  我要把那个红色的家伙塞进那个老头屁眼里
Now, I'm gonna shove the red guy up the old guy.
我相信他  人人为己了
I believe him! Every man for themselves!
扎到你了
Gotcha!
滚开  矮子
Beat it, midget!
嗨大家伙  太阳马上落山了
Hey, big guy, the sun's getting real low!
详见《复仇者联盟2》
哦我操
Oh, shit fuck!
过来  美人
Come here, beautiful.
说啊
Say it!
你来找我了
You came for me.
我不会放弃你
I'm not giving up on you,
你也不要放弃那个孩子
and you are not giving up on that boy.
谁说规则不是用来打破的
Who says that rules aren't meant to be broken?
现在该往脏里打了
It's time to fight dirty.
改走下三路了  强尼
Time to sweep the leg, Johnny.
喂  来打和你一般大小的人
Hey! Pick on someone your own size!
这真是你会说的话
That's such a you thing to say!
去干他  老虎
Go get him, tiger!
超级特效大战就要来了
Big CGI fight coming up!
他不错
He's doing great.
说
Say it!
- 罗素  - 发现了
- Russell. - Bingo!
是这样  我要脏着打
That's right! I'm fighting dirty!
真棒
Oh, great!
他们在那  那帮怪胎
There they are! Those freaks!
一帮穿着护士鞋的武装恋童癖
A bunch of armed pedophiles in nursing shoes.
这枪能给我一把呗
Can I have one of those guns?
- 不能  - 好吧
- No. - That's fine.
离开这个地方  变种人渣
Get off this property, mutant scum!
我就用这块砖头吧
I'm just gonna use this brick.
最大努力
Maximum effort.
谁说人不能回家的
Who says you can't go home again?
厉害
Yeah!
说啊
Say it.
说出你每次折磨我说的话
Say what you said every time you tortured me!
说
Say it!
愿上帝保佑经我手治愈之恶人
Blessed are the wicked who are healed by my hand!
愿上帝保佑
Blessed are the wicked...
经我手治愈
who are healed...
之恶人
by my hand.
你个苏联傻逼
You commie motherfucker!
哦我的天  你也感受到了吗
Oh, my God. Did you feel that, too?
只有铁哥们会一起处决恋童癖
Only best buddies execute pedophiles together.
给你三十秒  你这个啰啰嗦嗦的肛塞
You got 30 seconds, you jabbering butt plug!
这才对嘛
Now we're getting it.
我需要一辆大巴来把你们带走
I need a bus to get you all out of here.
孤儿们
Orphans.
哦天
Oh, geez.
是时候因你所为而被燃烧了
It's time to burn for what you've done!
一个小孩不应该承担这种能力
A child should not be burdened with such power!
罗素  等等
Russell! Wait!
等等  他还没有杀人呢
Wait! He hasn't killed anyone yet!
- 你还需要看到什么  - 你他妈的敢
- What more do you need to see? - Don't you fucking dare!
他只是个孩子
He's just a kid!
滴答  表打着呢
Tick, tock. Meter's running!
我要把你熔掉然后做成阴茎环
I'm gonna melt you down and make a cock ring.
- 我跟你说了  不要管我  - 好了
- I told you! Leave me alone! - Come on!
听我说
Listen to me!
我们在祖国俄罗斯
That's how we do it
就是这样做的
in Mother Russia.
他们说零零后最难沟通
They say millennials are the hardest to reach.
不是  你做得真棒
Oh, no. You're doing amazing.
干  当痞子的感觉真棒
Damn, it feels good to be a gangsta!
回家吧  韦德
Go home, Wade!
你要把一切都毁了
You're ruining everything!
我越来越擅长这玩意儿了
I'm getting good at this shit.
走走走
Go, go, go!
他今晚必死  韦德
He dies tonight, Wade.
你不能阻止我
You can't stop me!
他跑步都像个变态
He even runs like a fucking pervert.
像网上的恋童癖丢掉了笔记本电脑
Like an online predator who lost his laptop.
枪里还有一颗子弹
There's one bullet left in that gun.
等等  等等  求你  再给我一点时间
Wait, wait, wait! Please, just give me a second!
我能搞定
I got this.
- 罗素  - 退后  回家  韦德
- Russell! - Stay back! Go home, Wade!
咱们谈谈  不需要这样发展的
Let's talk. It doesn't have to go this way!
那个傻逼
That piece of shit...
应该为他对你做的事情去死
he deserves to die for what he did to you.
他狠狠地伤害了你  让你想伤害别人
He hurt you badly. Makes you wanna hurt others.
但如果你杀了他  他就赢了
But if you kill him, he wins.
你就变成了他说你是的东西  还更坏
You become everything he says you are, but worse.
你只是个孩子
You're just a kid.
你不想伤害别人的
You don't wanna hurt anyone.
你怎么知道我想做什么
How do you know what I want?
因为我在你体内过
Because I've been inside you.
这话不太对
That came out wrong.
我走过你的路
I've been inside your shoes.
这话也有点尴尬
Which is also off-putting.
不是什么好的比喻
It's not a great analogy.
重点是
The point is...
世界上
there are people...
世界上还有人
There are people in this fucking world...
除他以外的人  愿意对你好
besides him, who will treat you right.
还不晚  别杀他
It isn't too late. Don't do it.
我从来都不应该离开你的
I never should've left you there.
在监狱里我不应该离开你的
I never should've left you in that prison.
我不能信任你
I can't trust you.
我不能信任任何人
I can't trust anybody!
好孩子
Wonderful kid.
你阻止不了我  韦德
You can't stop me, Wade!
我还有个主意
I got one more idea.
只是这主意非常坏  对我来说都是
It's just a really bad one, even for me.
韦德  你要做什么
Wade, what are you doing?
好了  大奖都归我吧
All right. This is for all the marbles, kid!
你今天想杀人
You're gonna kill someone today...
愿上帝保佑
Blessed are the wicked...
那就杀我吧
then it's gotta be me.
经我手治愈之恶人
Who are healed by my hand!
我操
Fuck this!
太阳明天还会升起
* The sun will come out tomorrow
向你打赌一定会升起
* Bet your bottom dollar that tomorrow
太阳会出现
* There'll be sun
我困在一天里  灰暗又孤独
* When I'm stuck with a day that's gray and lonely
我露出下巴和牙齿笑着说
* I just stick out my chin and grin and say
太阳明天还会升起
* The sun will come out tomorrow
所以你要撑到明天
* So you gotta hang on till tomorrow
无论如何
* Come what may
明天  明天  我爱你  明天
* Tomorrow, tomorrow I love ya, tomorrow
你总是在一天之后
* You're always a day away
告诉我他们用慢动作拍下来了
Tell me they got that in slow motion.
哦  这可不好
Oh, that's not good.
可真不好
No, sir.
你为我牺牲了自己
You sacrificed yourself for me.
是啊
Yeah.
这是我做过的最好的事
And it was the best thing I ever did.
我告诉你了我在乎你
I told you I care about you.
你是个好孩子  罗素
You're a good kid, Russell.
喂
Hey.
小熊
The bear.
管用了
It worked.
因为你
Because of you.
不是  韦德  因为你
No, Wade, because of you.
停停停
Stop, stop, stop!
停
Stop!
就让我死吧  好吗
Just let it happen, okay?
我想我的心终于在正确的地方了
I guess my heart was finally in the right place.
这个谜语真差劲
That riddle is so fucked up.
我很抱歉  我很抱歉
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
没事  没事
Don't be. Don't be.
我早就想死了
I've been trying to make this happen for a while.
麻烦你们别离开我
Please, just don't leave me.
我不想在没有观众的时候死去
I don't wanna die without an audience.
我们哪也不去
We are not going anywhere.
哦天  我希望电影学会在看
Oh, God, I hope the Academy is watching.
休息吧  好吗
Just rest, okay?
爸爸
Papa.
爸爸  你能听到我吗
* Papa, can you hear me?
爸爸  你在晚上能找到我吗
* Papa, can you find me in the night?
我走之前
Before I go...
抱歉  我还有一口气
Sorry, I got a bit more in me.
多米诺
Domino.
我这块探险时光手表留给你
I want you to have my Adventure Time watch.
看来我才是最幸运的
Turns out that I'm the lucky one.
谢谢
Thank you.
嗨  小女巫萨布琳娜
Hey, Sabrina, the Teenage Witch.
和你共事很愉快
It has been a pleasure.
- 嗨雪绪  - 嗨韦德
- Hi, Yukio. - Hi, Wade!
还有你
And you...
铬金骨
Chrome Bone.
我不是一直很够朋友
I haven't always been the best friend to you.
但你一直陪在我身边
But you've always been that to me.
所以谢谢你
So thank you.
说句操给我听听
Say "fuck" for me.
就一次  来啊
Just once. Come on,
我们一起说  没啥大不了的
we'll do it together. It's no big deal.
来来来  一  二  三  呲  呲  呲
Here we go. One, two, three. F... F... F...
操
Fuck.
哇  等着下地狱吧  这嘴脏的
Wow! Enjoy hell, swamp mouth.
还有你  电索
And you, Cable.
你回去找你家人吧  你告诉他们韦德问好了
You get back to your family. You tell 'em Wade says hi.
然后答应我  答应我一件事
And promise me. Promise me one thing.
你从此评判人
That you'll start judging people...
不要通过他们的肤色
not by the color of their skin,
而是通过他们的人格
but by the content of their character.
- 天哪  - 阿罗
- Jesus. - R-Dog?
来来来
There you are. Hey!
你是个超级英雄了  小胖
You're a superhero now, bubba.
看
Look.
家庭才不是屁
Family is not an F-word.
明白吗
All right?
是陪伴你的人
There's one out there for you.
你接着寻找  好吗
Just keep looking, okay?
朋友们  有那么一瞬间
Guys, for a second there...
我们还是个不错的队伍
we made a pretty good team.
哦  死掉真难
Oh, it's so hard to go.
我只是很喜欢和你们在一起
I just love being around you guys so much.
非常非常喜欢
So, so much.
嗯
Mmm.
我能感觉到了  来了来了  嗯
No, I can feel it now. Here it comes, yeah.
我感觉到灵魂离开了躯壳
I feel the soul exiting the husk.
嗯
Yeah.
你能看到吗
Can you see it?
你能看见那美丽的亮光吗
Do you see that beautiful bright light?
就在那儿
There it is.
哦  那是太阳
Oh, that's the sun.
不要盯着看
Don't stare directly into that.
我最后还有几句话
I just have a few final words.
啄木鸟
Woodpecker.
牙龈炎
Gingivitis.
废话
Codswallop.
你想不想堆雪人
Do You Want to Build a Snowman?
我们一直在聊
* We're talking away
我却不知道要说什么
* I don't know what I'm to say
我就说了
* I'll say it anyway
今天又是一个去找你的一天
* Today's another day to find you
避开
* Shying away
我去找你的爱  好吗
* I'll be coming for your love, okay?
迎接我
* Take on me
接纳我
* Take me on
对不起  我来晚了
Sorry I'm late.
有一帮
There was a bunch
不残不疾的小孩困在了一棵树上
of handicapable children who were stuck in a tree.
- 不对  - 不对
- No. - No.
- 但我必须要帮那个孩子  - 是的
- But I did have to help a kid. - Yeah.
- 他名字烂透了  - 确实很烂
- He's got a terrible name. - It's just awful.
- 呃  - 我想告诉他来着
- Ugh. - I tried to tell him.
这是天堂吗
Is this heaven?
现在是了
It is now.
对不起
I am so sorry.
没关系
It's okay.
慢慢了解  生活很好
* Slowly learning that life is okay
跟我说
* Say after me
安全总比后悔好
* It's no better to be safe than sorry
迎接我
* Take on me
我很想你
I missed you so much.
这是什么  怎么了
What is it? What's wrong?
现在不是时候
It's not time.
什么叫现在不是时候
What do you mean it's not time?
我在这里  我来了
I'm here, I made it.
- 你不能留下  - 不  不  不
- You can't stay. - No, no, no.
我要留下来  没有你  我哪都不去
I'm staying. I'm not going anywhere without you.
没事的
It's okay.
我们有时间相处  只是现在不行
There's a time for us. It's just not now.
- 他们需要你  - 谁
- They need you. - Who?
你的屁
Your F-word.
为什么
Why?
你会明白的
You'll find out.
没事的  我一直在这里
It's all right. I'll be here.
我爱你
I love you.
我知道  我也爱你
I know. I love you, too.
现在去吧
Now, go.
去吧  快离开这里
Go on. Go, get out of here.
去吧
Go.
嘿
Hey!
快来狠狠亲我  小红
Kiss me like you miss me, Red.
过来
Well, come here.
接纳我
* Take me on
我就离开
* I'll be gone
一两天
* In a day or two
别和猫王上床
Don't fuck Elvis.
- 别和钢力士上床  - 什么
- Don't fuck Colossus. - What?
该去创造奇迹了
Time to make the chimichangas.
三十秒
30 seconds.
喂  一直想问你
Hey. Been meaning to ask you...
这个诡异的  肮脏的流浪熊是啥
what's with the creepy, dirty hobo bear?
那是我女儿的泰迪熊
It's my daughter's teddy bear.
她叫霍普
Her name's Hope.
喔
Well...
你在干什么
What are you doing?
你右划了嘛
Somebody swiped right.
告诉我他们用慢动作拍下来了
Tell me they got that in slow motion.
你为我牺牲了自己
You sacrificed yourself for me.
看上去我
It would seem I...
哈
Huh?
真的  高级别铅
Genuine, high-grade lead.
你这个穿越的混蛋
You time-sliding son of a bitch!
这是你为我做的
You did this for me?
等等  你不能再回去了
Wait. You can't go back.
你用掉了最后的燃料
You used the last of your fuel.
那你的女儿  妻子怎么办
What about your girl, your wife?
我的家庭现在很安全  而且我不是为你才这么做的
Now, my family's safe. And I didn't do it for you.
现在  我得在这里待上一阵子
No, I'm gonna stick around for a while...
确保这个世界
and make sure the world
不会被自己毁掉
doesn't shit itself into oblivion.
不  你就是为了我
No. You did it for me.
不  我没有
No, I didn't.
- 就是  - 我真的没有
- You did. - I really didn't.
- 很确定就是  - 不  我肯定没有
- Pretty sure you did. - No, I'm positive I didn't.
那好吧  我们掷硬币决定  好吗
Fine. All right, let's flip a coin. Okay?
正面  是你为我  反面  是你为我
Heads, you did it for me. Tails, you did it for me.
我都懒得看  因为你就是为了我
I'm not even gonna look, because you did it for me.
再说一遍
Say it again.
- 他是为了我  - 天啊
- He did it for me. - Jesus.
- 我们得把项圈摘掉  - 别想了  没用的
- We must get the collar off. - Forget it. It's no use.
这些项圈不容易脱
These collars don't just come off.
韦德
Wade.
我有个主意
I have an idea.
不  不  不  请不要这么做
No, no, no! Let's not do that. Please!
我宁愿得癌症死掉  我们只要
I'd rather die of cancer. Let's just...
哦  天啊  他们说笔比剑更恶心
Oh, God! They do say the pen is grosser than the sword.
我们需要密码
We need the code.
试试  呃  七
Try, uh, seven?
好了  幸运队长
Settle down, Captain Lucky.
不可能只是一个数字
It's not gonna be one number.
哦  天啊  编剧又犯懒了
Oh, God, that's lazy writing.
看来我还是幸运
I still got it.
把那个放回你的监狱钱包里
Put that back in your prison wallet.
我不知道如何感谢你
I don't know how to thank you.
但我知道如何拥抱你
But I do know how to hug you.
- 不  - 来吧
- No. - Yes.
来吧来吧
Here we go. Bring it in.
来吧
Come on.
骨盆对骨盆
Pelvis to pelvis.
尖对尖
Let's go tip to tip.
好了  孩子们称之为对接
There we go. The kids call this docking.
你拿刀子顶着我的屌呢吗
Is there a knife in my dick?
- 我拿刀子顶着你的屌呢  - 我现在就回去
- There's a knife in your dick. - I'm just gonna back up now.
- 是的  是的  - 没必要来个《燕特尔》
- Yeah, yeah. - No need to go full Yentl.
装作没发生过
Gonna pretend like that never happened.
我们回家吧  罗素
Let's go home, Russell.
你们这些肮脏的变种人
All you dirty mutants
都会和那个小子一起在地狱里腐烂
are gonna rot in hell with the boy!
你们的灵魂无法得到救赎
Your souls are beyond redemption!
让我们看看你的灵魂  老变态
Let's see your soul, perv!
不  不  不  不要  我们比那要强
No, no! No! No more! We're better than that!
因为我们比他强
We're better than him!
不要再有无谓的暴力  不要再流血
No more senseless violence! No more bloodshed!
他自有因果报应
We'll let karma take care of him.
清算的日子到了
The day of reckoning is here!
我会想念他的  他看起来像个好人
I'm gonna miss him. He seemed great.
喔
Whoo!
勇气了  傻逼们
Courage, motherfuckers!
报应啊  傻逼们
And karma, motherfucker.
我三十秒前就听到你了
I could hear you coming the last 30 seconds.
我都没法保持严肃
I could barely keep a straight face.
我还想要
I want some more.
我知道你想  棕豹
I bet you do, Brown Panther.
我们应该在那个傻逼醒来之前离开
We should leave before Fuckernaut wakes up.
好主意  你们跟我们一起走吗
Good call. You guys coming with us?
不  我们要把孩子们带回去
No, we'll get the kids back to the mansion.
毕竟  我们是X战警
Besides, we're X-Men.
不  你是X人类
No, you're X-People.
你是X累人
You're exhausting.
我明白你说的意思  是双关语
I see what you did there. Puns.
- 拜  韦德  - 拜  雪绪
- Bye, Wade! - Bye, Yukio!
这个组合
What do you get
两米四的铬
when you take eight feet of chrome...
加一点点勇气
one pinch of courage...
加一杯好运
a cup of good luck...
加少许种族歧视
a dab of racism...
加一丢丢糖尿病
a splash of diabetes...
再加一车四级癌症  出来什么呢
and a wheelbarrow full of stage four cancer?
答案是一个家庭
Answer is a family.
看见了吗  我说这是个合家欢电影
See? I didn't lie what kind of film this was.
如果今天你能有任何收获的话
If there's anything you take away today...
除了要去谷歌“回响贝斯是他妈啥玩意”
other than the need to Google, "What the fuck is dubstep?"...
那就是我们都需要属于某人
it's that we all need to belong to someone.
死于泡泡浴
侍  死侍
拜拜 朋友们
开机
坦克画的不错
跳舞 小锡人 跳舞
我他妈叫什么名字
狗日的生活
小熊维尼风
给死侍笑一个
待办事项
1.世界和平
2.打给都朋德
3.杀坏人
这位身上的X力很强
要赚钱了
死侍2
这么小的东西
How something so small generates
怎么能产生足够的能量来逆转时间呢
enough energy to reverse time is...
你就修好它  小11
Oh, just fix it, Eleven,
不然我带去天才吧了
or I'll take it to the Genius Bar.
电索要是发现的话会杀了你
Cable's gonna kill you when he finds out.
谁  没听说过
Never heard of him.
你为什么觉得我要帮他
Why do you think I'm helping him?
上帝以神秘的方式工作
The Lord works in mysterious ways,
我不是吗  美好的一天
don't I? A good day.
拜  韦德
Bye, Wade!
拜  雪绪
Bye, Yukio!
这可能是个坏主意
That was probably a bad idea.
我们做了什么
What have we done?
我希望我们把奶油刀磨快乐
I hope we sharpened the cream cheese spreader.
我马上回来
I'll be right back!
我们一定要给孩子取名雪儿
We're definitely naming our kid Cher!
喔
Whoo!
彼得
Peter!
喔  X特攻队
Whoo! X-Force!
走开  快走开
Walk away! Just walk away!
但我们是X特攻队
But we're X-Force!
不  我们不是  没有什么X特攻队
Nope! We're not, there's no X-Force!
好吧  这一路上挺吓人的
All right, well, this has been pretty scary!
回家吧  小熊甜心  回家
Go home, Sugarbear. Go home.
好的  你能把我的邮件地址给多米诺吗
Okay. Will you give Domino my email?
韦德  是你吗
Wade, is that you?
我猜史崔克
I guess Stryker finally
终于想出办法让你闭嘴了
figured out how to shut you up.
嘿  是我  别抓我
Hey! It's me! Don't scratch!
只是清理一下时间线
Just cleaning up the timelines!
爱你
Love you!
欢迎加入大联盟  孩子
Welcome to the big leagues, kid.
绿灯侠
不客气  加拿大
You're welcome, Canada.
■
人人视频APP
在线观看美剧
离线高清缓存
更有海量高清电影
扫码即刻下载
特别推荐
■
各大应用市场均可下载
m 423 280 b 423 289 423 297 423 305 415 305 407 305 398 305 398 297 398 289 398 280 406 280 414 280 423 280 m 190 488 b 198 488 206 488 215 488 215 496 215 504 215 513 207 513 199 513 190 513 190 505 190 496 190 488 m 190 280 b 199 280 207 280 215 280 215 288 215 296 215 305 207 305 199 305 190 305 190 297 190 289 190 280 m 391 472 b 391 475 391 478 391 481 388 481 385 481 382 481 382 478 382 475 382 472 385 472 388 472 391 472 m 430 529 b 430 526 430 523 430 520 433 520 436 520 439 520 439 523 439 526 439 529 436 529 433 529 430 529 m 439 504 b 440 513 440 514 430 513 430 510 430 507 430 504 433 504 436 504 439 504 m 431 497 b 428 497 425 497 422 497 422 494 422 491 422 488 425 488 428 488 431 488 431 491 431 494 431 497 m 238 489 b 238 486 238 483 238 480 241 480 244 480 247 480 247 483 247 486 247 489 244 489 241 489 238 489 m 375 312 b 375 315 375 318 375 321 372 321 369 321 366 321 366 318 366 315 366 312 369 312 372 312 375 312 m 238 504 b 241 504 244 504 247 504 247 512 247 520 247 529 246 529 246 529 245 529 238 529 238 529 238 522 238 516 238 510 238 504 m 439 449 b 436 449 433 449 430 449 430 446 430 444 430 441 428 441 426 441 423 441 423 444 423 446 423 449 420 449 417 449 414 449 414 446 414 443 414 440 417 440 419 440 422 440 422 437 422 435 422 432 425 432 427 432 430 432 430 429 430 427 430 424 433 424 436 424 439 424 439 432 439 441 439 449 m 430 417 b 430 414 430 412 430 409 422 409 414 409 406 409 406 403 406 398 406 392 409 392 412 392 415 392 415 395 415 397 415 400 420 400 425 400 430 400 430 397 430 395 430 392 433 392 436 392 439 392 439 400 439 408 439 417 436 417 433 417 430 417 m 255 280 b 255 283 255 286 255 289 252 289 249 289 246 289 246 286 246 284 246 281 243 281 241 281 238 281 238 275 238 270 238 264 249 264 260 264 271 264 271 270 271 275 271 280 268 280 265 280 262 280 262 278 262 276 262 273 257 273 252 273 247 273 247 275 247 277 247 280 250 280 252 280 255 280 m 174 344 b 180 344 185 344 190 344 190 341 190 340 190 337 185 337 180 337 174 337 174 334 174 331 174 328 182 328 190 328 199 328 199 334 199 339 199 345 196 345 194 345 191 345 191 348 191 350 191 353 188 353 186 353 183 353 183 358 183 364 183 369 180 369 177 369 174 369 174 361 174 353 174 344 m 422 328 b 428 328 433 328 439 328 439 336 439 344 439 353 433 353 428 353 422 353 422 350 422 348 422 345 420 345 418 345 415 345 415 348 415 350 415 353 409 353 404 353 398 353 398 350 398 347 398 344 403 344 409 344 414 344 414 341 414 339 414 336 417 336 419 336 422 336 422 333 422 331 422 328 m 391 312 b 405 312 417 312 430 312 430 299 430 286 430 273 417 273 404 273 391 273 391 286 391 299 391 312 m 439 321 b 420 321 401 321 382 321 382 302 382 283 382 264 401 264 420 264 439 264 439 283 439 302 439 321 m 183 481 b 183 495 183 507 183 520 196 520 209 520 222 520 222 507 222 494 222 481 209 481 196 481 183 481 m 174 472 b 193 472 212 472 231 472 231 491 231 510 231 529 212 529 194 529 174 529 174 510 174 491 174 472 m 183 312 b 196 312 209 312 222 312 222 299 222 286 222 273 209 273 196 273 183 273 183 286 183 299 183 312 m 231 321 b 212 321 193 321 174 321 174 302 174 283 174 264 193 264 212 264 231 264 231 283 231 302 231 321 m 343 280 b 346 280 348 280 350 280 350 277 350 275 350 273 347 273 345 273 343 273 343 275 343 277 343 280 m 302 424 b 302 421 302 419 302 417 299 417 297 417 295 417 295 420 295 422 295 424 298 424 299 424 302 424 m 295 513 b 295 516 295 518 295 520 298 520 300 520 302 520 302 518 302 515 302 513 299 513 298 513 295 513 m 254 360 b 254 357 254 355 254 353 251 353 249 353 247 353 247 356 247 358 247 360 249 360 251 360 254 360 m 247 464 b 250 464 252 464 254 464 254 461 254 459 254 457 251 457 249 457 247 457 247 460 247 462 247 464 m 255 449 b 255 452 255 454 255 456 258 456 260 456 262 456 262 453 262 452 262 449 260 449 258 449 255 449 m 239 456 b 242 456 244 456 246 456 246 453 246 452 246 449 244 449 241 449 239 449 239 452 239 454 239 456 m 247 441 b 247 444 247 446 247 448 250 448 252 448 253 448 253 445 253 443 253 441 251 441 249 441 247 441 m 231 441 b 231 444 231 446 231 448 234 448 236 448 237 448 237 445 237 443 237 441 235 441 233 441 231 441 m 230 440 b 230 437 230 435 230 433 227 433 225 433 223 433 223 436 223 438 223 440 226 440 228 440 230 440 m 247 409 b 247 411 247 414 247 416 250 416 251 416 253 416 253 413 253 411 253 409 251 409 250 409 247 409 m 223 360 b 226 360 228 360 230 360 230 357 230 355 230 353 227 353 225 353 223 353 223 356 223 357 223 360 m 254 313 b 251 313 249 313 247 313 247 316 247 318 247 320 250 320 252 320 254 320 254 317 254 316 254 313 m 279 304 b 282 304 284 304 286 304 286 301 286 299 286 297 283 297 281 297 279 297 279 300 279 301 279 304 m 230 385 b 227 385 225 385 223 385 223 388 223 390 223 392 226 392 228 392 230 392 230 389 230 387 230 385 m 231 393 b 231 396 231 398 231 400 234 400 236 400 238 400 238 397 238 395 238 393 235 393 234 393 231 393 m 303 512 b 306 512 308 512 310 512 310 509 310 507 310 505 307 505 305 505 303 505 303 508 303 509 303 512 m 335 416 b 338 416 340 416 342 416 342 413 342 411 342 409 339 409 337 409 335 409 335 412 335 414 335 416 m 358 281 b 356 281 353 281 351 281 351 286 351 291 351 296 354 296 356 296 358 296 358 291 358 286 358 281 m 207 361 b 208 364 205 367 209 368 213 369 217 368 221 368 221 365 221 363 221 361 216 361 212 361 207 361 m 344 417 b 344 422 344 427 344 432 346 432 348 432 350 432 350 429 350 427 350 424 353 424 355 424 358 424 358 421 358 419 358 417 353 417 348 417 344 417 m 183 409 b 183 414 183 419 183 424 186 424 188 424 190 424 190 421 190 419 190 416 193 416 195 416 198 416 198 413 198 411 198 409 193 409 188 409 183 409 m 270 385 b 265 385 260 385 255 385 255 388 255 390 255 393 252 393 250 393 247 393 247 396 247 398 247 400 252 400 257 400 262 400 262 397 262 395 262 392 265 392 267 392 270 392 270 389 270 387 270 385 m 383 512 b 386 512 388 512 391 512 391 515 391 517 391 520 396 520 401 520 406 520 406 517 406 515 406 513 403 513 401 513 398 513 398 510 398 508 398 505 395 505 393 505 390 505 390 502 390 500 390 497 385 497 380 497 375 497 375 500 375 502 375 504 378 504 380 504 383 504 383 507 383 509 383 512 m 246 392 b 246 381 246 371 246 361 243 361 241 361 239 361 239 364 239 366 239 369 233 369 228 369 223 369 223 372 223 374 223 376 226 376 228 376 231 376 231 379 231 381 231 384 234 384 236 384 239 384 239 387 239 389 239 392 242 392 244 392 246 392 m 326 321 b 323 321 321 321 318 321 318 318 318 316 318 313 315 313 313 313 311 313 311 316 311 318 311 321 308 321 306 321 303 321 303 326 303 331 303 336 311 336 318 336 326 336 326 331 326 326 326 321 m 398 465 b 390 465 383 465 376 465 376 473 376 480 376 488 383 488 390 488 398 488 398 480 398 473 398 465 m 231 432 b 239 432 247 432 255 432 255 435 255 437 255 440 258 440 260 440 262 440 262 432 262 425 262 417 260 417 257 417 255 417 255 420 255 422 255 425 249 425 244 425 238 425 238 419 238 414 238 409 235 409 233 409 231 409 231 412 231 414 231 417 228 417 226 417 223 417 223 420 223 422 223 424 226 424 228 424 231 424 231 427 231 429 231 432 m 191 425 b 191 427 190 431 191 431 193 432 196 432 199 433 199 440 199 448 199 456 210 456 220 456 230 456 230 453 230 452 230 449 225 449 219 449 214 449 214 446 214 444 214 441 211 441 209 441 206 441 206 438 206 435 206 432 209 432 211 432 214 432 214 427 214 422 214 417 211 417 209 417 207 417 207 420 207 422 207 425 201 425 196 425 191 425 m 278 481 b 278 476 278 471 278 465 276 465 273 465 271 465 271 471 271 476 271 481 268 481 266 481 263 481 263 486 263 491 263 496 269 496 274 496 279 496 279 499 279 501 279 504 282 504 284 504 287 504 287 507 287 509 287 512 290 512 292 512 294 512 294 506 294 501 294 496 297 496 299 496 302 496 302 494 302 492 302 489 296 489 291 489 286 489 286 486 286 484 286 481 283 481 281 481 278 481 m 231 352 b 236 352 241 352 246 352 246 349 246 347 246 344 252 344 257 344 263 344 263 347 263 349 263 352 266 352 267 352 270 352 270 347 270 342 270 337 267 337 265 337 262 337 262 334 262 331 262 328 268 328 273 328 279 328 279 331 279 333 279 336 282 336 284 336 286 336 286 333 286 331 286 328 289 328 291 328 294 328 294 325 294 323 294 321 291 321 289 321 286 321 286 318 286 316 286 313 283 313 281 313 279 313 279 316 279 318 279 321 276 321 273 321 270 321 270 315 270 310 270 305 267 305 265 305 263 305 263 311 263 316 263 321 260 321 258 321 255 321 255 327 255 332 255 337 249 337 244 337 239 337 239 340 239 342 239 345 236 345 234 345 231 345 231 347 231 349 231 352 m 343 384 b 343 392 343 400 343 408 346 408 348 408 350 408 350 405 350 403 350 400 356 400 361 400 366 400 366 397 366 395 366 392 369 392 371 392 374 392 374 387 374 382 374 377 371 377 369 377 367 377 367 380 367 382 367 385 364 385 362 385 359 385 359 388 359 390 359 393 356 393 353 393 350 393 350 384 350 376 350 368 356 368 361 368 366 368 366 363 366 358 366 353 360 353 355 353 350 353 350 350 350 348 350 345 345 345 340 345 335 345 335 348 335 350 335 352 338 352 341 352 343 352 343 355 343 358 343 361 340 361 337 361 334 361 334 358 334 356 334 353 328 353 323 353 318 353 318 350 318 348 318 345 315 345 314 345 311 345 311 353 311 360 311 368 314 368 316 368 319 368 319 371 319 373 319 376 322 376 324 376 326 376 326 373 326 371 326 368 329 368 332 368 335 368 335 374 335 379 335 384 338 384 340 384 343 384 m 207 408 b 210 408 212 408 215 408 215 411 215 413 215 416 217 416 219 416 222 416 222 413 222 411 222 408 225 408 227 408 230 408 230 406 230 404 230 401 227 401 225 401 222 401 222 398 222 396 222 393 219 393 217 393 214 393 214 388 214 383 214 377 209 377 204 377 199 377 199 380 199 382 199 385 196 385 193 385 190 385 190 377 190 369 190 360 195 360 200 360 206 360 206 355 206 349 206 344 214 344 222 344 230 344 230 342 230 340 230 337 225 337 220 337 214 337 214 334 214 331 214 328 220 328 225 328 231 328 231 331 231 333 231 336 233 336 235 336 238 336 238 323 238 310 238 296 241 296 244 296 247 296 247 299 247 301 247 304 252 304 257 304 262 304 262 299 262 294 262 288 267 288 272 288 278 288 278 285 278 283 278 280 281 280 283 280 286 280 286 275 286 270 286 264 289 264 292 264 295 264 295 270 295 275 295 281 292 281 290 281 287 281 287 284 287 286 287 288 290 288 292 288 295 288 295 294 295 299 295 305 292 305 290 305 287 305 287 307 287 309 287 312 290 312 292 312 295 312 295 315 295 317 295 320 297 320 299 320 302 320 302 317 302 315 302 312 305 312 307 312 310 312 310 309 310 307 310 304 313 304 315 304 318 304 318 302 318 299 318 297 312 297 307 297 302 297 302 291 302 286 302 280 307 280 312 280 318 280 318 275 318 270 318 264 321 264 324 264 327 264 327 270 327 275 327 281 324 281 322 281 319 281 319 286 319 291 319 295 321 295 323 295 326 295 326 293 326 291 326 288 329 288 332 288 335 288 335 291 335 294 335 297 332 297 330 297 327 297 327 305 327 312 327 320 329 320 331 320 334 320 334 315 334 310 334 304 339 304 344 304 350 304 350 302 350 300 350 297 347 297 345 297 342 297 342 291 342 287 342 281 339 281 337 281 334 281 334 278 334 275 334 272 337 272 339 272 342 272 342 269 342 267 342 264 348 264 353 264 359 264 359 269 359 274 359 280 362 280 364 280 367 280 367 286 367 291 367 297 364 297 362 297 359 297 359 305 359 313 359 321 356 321 353 321 350 321 350 318 350 316 350 313 348 313 346 313 343 313 343 316 343 318 343 321 340 321 338 321 335 321 335 323 335 325 335 328 338 328 340 328 343 328 343 331 343 333 343 336 346 336 348 336 351 336 351 339 351 341 351 344 353 344 356 344 358 344 358 338 358 333 358 328 361 328 364 328 367 328 367 331 367 333 367 336 369 336 371 336 374 336 374 333 374 331 374 328 385 328 396 328 407 328 407 331 407 334 407 337 402 337 397 337 391 337 391 340 391 342 391 344 388 344 385 344 382 344 382 342 382 340 382 337 380 337 378 337 375 337 375 340 375 342 375 345 372 345 370 345 367 345 367 347 367 349 367 352 370 352 372 352 375 352 375 360 375 368 375 376 377 376 379 376 382 376 382 368 382 360 382 352 385 352 388 352 391 352 391 357 391 362 391 368 394 368 396 368 399 368 399 371 399 373 399 376 401 376 403 376 406 376 406 371 406 365 406 360 409 360 412 360 415 360 415 363 415 365 415 368 417 368 419 368 422 368 422 365 422 363 422 360 428 360 433 360 439 360 439 368 439 376 439 385 436 385 433 385 430 385 430 383 430 380 430 377 422 377 415 377 407 377 407 380 407 382 407 385 404 385 401 385 398 385 398 382 398 380 398 377 396 377 394 377 392 377 392 385 392 392 392 400 394 400 396 400 399 400 399 405 399 410 399 416 404 416 409 416 415 416 415 422 415 427 415 433 412 433 409 433 406 433 406 430 406 428 406 425 404 425 402 425 399 425 399 428 399 430 399 433 397 433 394 433 392 433 392 435 392 437 392 440 396 440 402 440 407 440 407 443 407 446 407 449 401 449 396 449 390 449 390 446 390 444 390 441 387 441 385 441 382 441 382 436 382 431 382 425 379 425 377 425 374 425 374 422 374 419 374 416 380 416 384 416 390 416 390 414 390 412 390 409 387 409 385 409 382 409 382 404 382 399 382 393 380 393 378 393 375 393 375 398 375 403 375 409 372 409 370 409 367 409 367 417 367 424 367 432 370 432 372 432 375 432 375 435 375 438 375 441 373 441 370 441 367 441 367 443 367 445 367 448 372 448 377 448 383 448 383 451 383 453 383 456 394 456 404 456 415 456 415 459 415 461 415 464 417 464 419 464 422 464 422 461 422 459 422 456 425 456 428 456 431 456 431 459 431 461 431 464 434 464 436 464 439 464 439 470 439 475 439 481 436 481 433 481 430 481 430 476 430 471 430 465 428 465 426 465 423 465 423 468 423 470 423 473 420 473 418 473 415 473 415 481 415 489 415 497 412 497 410 497 407 497 407 502 407 507 407 512 410 512 412 512 414 512 414 509 414 507 414 504 417 504 420 504 423 504 423 507 423 510 423 513 420 513 418 513 415 513 415 516 415 518 415 521 412 521 410 521 408 521 408 522 407 522 407 522 407 529 407 529 400 529 397 529 394 529 390 529 390 526 390 524 390 521 385 521 381 521 375 521 375 524 375 526 375 529 372 529 369 529 366 529 366 523 366 518 366 512 369 512 371 512 374 512 374 510 374 508 374 505 369 505 365 505 359 505 359 510 359 515 359 521 356 521 353 521 350 521 350 516 350 511 350 505 345 505 340 505 335 505 335 507 335 509 335 512 338 512 340 512 343 512 343 518 343 523 343 529 337 529 332 529 326 529 326 518 326 507 326 496 329 496 331 496 334 496 334 494 334 492 334 489 329 489 324 489 318 489 318 486 318 483 318 480 321 480 323 480 326 480 326 472 326 464 326 456 332 456 337 456 343 456 343 461 343 467 343 472 346 472 348 472 350 472 350 469 350 467 350 464 353 464 356 464 359 464 359 470 359 475 359 481 354 481 349 481 344 481 344 486 344 491 344 496 346 496 348 496 351 496 351 499 351 501 351 504 353 504 356 504 358 504 358 499 358 493 358 488 361 488 363 488 366 488 366 478 366 468 366 457 361 457 356 457 350 457 350 454 350 451 350 448 353 448 355 448 358 448 358 446 358 444 358 441 350 441 343 441 335 441 335 444 335 446 335 449 332 449 329 449 326 449 326 443 326 438 326 432 329 432 331 432 334 432 334 427 334 422 334 417 332 417 330 417 327 417 327 420 327 422 327 425 324 425 321 425 318 425 318 422 318 419 318 416 321 416 323 416 326 416 326 408 326 400 326 392 329 392 331 392 334 392 334 390 334 388 334 385 326 385 318 385 310 385 310 380 310 375 310 369 308 369 305 369 303 369 303 375 303 380 303 385 300 385 298 385 295 385 295 388 295 390 295 393 292 393 289 393 286 393 286 385 286 377 286 368 291 368 296 368 302 368 302 366 302 363 302 361 299 361 297 361 294 361 294 353 294 345 294 337 292 337 290 337 287 337 287 340 287 342 287 345 284 345 282 345 279 345 279 353 279 361 279 369 276 369 273 369 270 369 270 366 270 364 270 361 268 361 266 361 263 361 263 366 263 371 263 376 268 376 273 376 279 376 279 384 279 392 279 400 282 400 284 400 287 400 287 403 287 406 287 409 284 409 282 409 279 409 279 412 279 414 279 417 276 417 274 417 271 417 271 422 271 427 271 432 274 432 276 432 279 432 279 435 279 438 279 441 276 441 274 441 271 441 271 446 271 451 271 456 274 456 276 456 279 456 279 459 279 461 279 464 282 464 284 464 287 464 287 467 287 469 287 472 289 472 291 472 294 472 294 469 294 467 294 464 297 464 299 464 302 464 302 459 302 455 302 450 300 450 298 450 295 450 295 452 295 454 295 457 292 457 289 457 286 457 286 451 286 446 286 440 289 440 291 440 294 440 294 435 294 430 294 425 291 425 289 425 286 425 286 422 286 419 286 416 289 416 291 416 294 416 294 411 294 406 294 400 297 400 299 400 302 400 302 397 302 395 302 392 305 392 308 392 311 392 311 395 311 397 311 400 314 400 316 400 319 400 319 403 319 406 319 409 314 409 309 409 303 409 303 411 303 413 303 416 306 416 308 416 311 416 311 422 311 426 311 432 314 432 316 432 319 432 319 435 319 438 319 441 314 441 308 441 303 441 303 443 303 445 303 448 306 448 308 448 311 448 311 456 311 464 311 473 308 473 306 473 303 473 303 475 303 477 303 480 306 480 308 480 311 480 311 488 311 496 311 504 314 504 316 504 319 504 319 507 319 510 319 513 316 513 314 513 311 513 311 516 311 518 311 521 308 521 306 521 303 521 303 524 303 526 303 529 300 529 297 529 294 529 294 526 294 524 294 521 291 521 289 521 286 521 286 518 286 516 286 513 283 513 282 513 279 513 279 516 279 518 279 521 276 521 274 521 271 521 271 524 271 526 271 529 268 529 265 529 262 529 262 526 262 523 262 520 265 520 267 520 270 520 270 518 270 516 270 513 267 513 265 513 262 513 262 510 262 508 262 505 259 505 257 505 254 505 254 497 254 489 254 480 257 480 259 480 262 480 262 475 262 470 262 465 260 465 258 465 255 465 255 468 255 470 255 473 249 473 244 473 238 473 238 468 238 462 238 457 235 457 234 457 231 457 231 460 231 462 231 465 220 465 209 465 198 465 198 462 198 460 198 457 196 457 194 457 191 457 191 460 191 462 191 465 185 465 180 465 174 465 174 462 174 459 174 456 180 456 185 456 190 456 190 454 190 452 190 449 185 449 180 449 174 449 174 446 174 443 174 440 177 440 179 440 182 440 182 435 182 430 182 425 179 425 177 425 174 425 174 411 174 398 174 384 177 384 180 384 183 384 183 390 183 395 183 400 191 400 198 400 206 400 207 403 207 405 207 408
m 280   389   b 280   389   280   389   280 389   280 391   280 393   280 396   280   395   280   395   280   395   281   394   283   393   284   392   284   392   284   392   284   392   283   391   281   390   280   389   m 281   384   b 286   384   290   388   290   392   290   397   286   401   281   401   277   400   273   397   273   392   273   388 277   384   281   384   m 255   383   b 255   378   255   374   255   370   255   370   255   370   256   370   260   370   265   370   270   370   271   370   273   370   274   371   276   372   277   373   278   375   278   376   278   377   278   378   277   380   276   381   274   382   272   382   271   382   270   383   265   383   260   383   255   383   255   383   255   383   255   383   m 295   398   b 295   393   295   389   295   385   295   385   295   385   296   385   300   385   305   385   310   385   311   385   313   386   315   386   316   387   318   388   318   390   318   391   318   392   318   393   317   395   316   396   314   397   313 397   311   398   310   398   305   398   300   398   295   398   295   398   295   398   295   398   m 291   367   b 291   367   291   367   291   367   290   364   288   362   285   361   283   360   281   360   279   360   277   359   275   359   273   359   263   359   253   359   243   359   242   359   242   359   242   359   242   360   242   360   242   360   242   378   242   397   242   416   242   417   242   417   243   417   247   417   250   417   253   417   254   417   255   416   255   415   255   412   255   408   255   405   255   401   255   397   255   394   255   393   255   393   256   393   257   393   258   393   260   393   263   393   265   395   267   396   270   399   272   402   273   405   274   406   274   406   273   406   272   410   270   413   269   416   266   421   264   427   262   432   262 432   261   432   261   433   261   433   262   434   262   434   263   434   264   434   264   433   266   429 268   424   270   419   273   414   276   408   278   402   278   402   278   402   279   402   280   402   280   402   281   402   284   402   287   401   289   398   290   398   290   398   290   398   290   398   290   398   290   398   289   401   286   403   283   403   282   403   282   403   282   404   282   404   282   404   282   404   282   413   282   422   282   431   282   432   282   432   283   432   287   432   290   432   293   432   294   432   295   431   295   430   295   423   295   416   295   409   295   408   295   408   296   408   297   408   298   408   299   408   300   408   302   408   304   409   307   411   309   413   310   415   313   419   315   423   316   427   316   428   316   429   317   430   317   431   318   432   319   432   323   432   327   432   331   432   332   432   332   432   333   432   333   432   334   431   333   431   333   430   333   430   333   430   331   424   329   419   326   414   325   412   323   410   321   408   321   407   320   407   319   406   320   406   321   406   322   406   325   405   328   403   330   400   333   396   333   392   333   388   333   386   332   383   330   381   329   378   326   376   323   375   321   375   319   375   316   375   309   375   302   375   295   375   295   375   295   375   295   375   293   378   292   380   291   383   291   384   290   385   290   386   289   385   288   385   287   384   287   384   287   383   287   383   288   381   289   379   290   377   293   371   296   364   299   357   299   357   299   356   298   356   298 355   297   355   296   356   296   358   295   360   294   361   293   363   292   365   291   367   m 234   438   b 234   410   234   382 234   353   234   353   234   353   234   353   235 348   237   344   242   343   243   342   244   342   245   342   273   342   301   342   329   342   330 342   330   342   330   342   335   343   338   346   340   351   340   352   340   352   341   353   341   382 341   410   341   438   341   438   341   438   341   438   340   443   336   447   331   449   331   449   330   449   329   449   301   449   273   449   245   449   245   449   244   449   244   449   239   448   236   445   234   440   234   440   234   439   234   438
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手）
另：招募长期居住加拿大、美国的童鞋帮忙录制CC字幕（有偿）